Daddy, may I have a piece of candy?
This is the last one.
'Kay!
You okay?
My butt hurts!
We're almost there.
But what if some magical beasts attack?
Don't worry. The mercenaries
and witches will take care of them.
Yeah, you're right!
We've arrived, ladies and gentlemen.
This is the start of our new life!
Here you go.
Thanks, come again!
May I get one, as well?
Sure thing.
Don't think I've seen you before.
You from out of town, miss?
Yes. From Bristol.
Bristol, eh? That must've been quite the trip.
I was asleep, so it felt like mere moments.
Here you are.
Oh, I need to pay you.
Hold it right there!
You're a cute gal, so it's on the house.
Huh? But...
Allow me to officially
welcome you to Malmcester!
Yummy.
What do you think you're doing?!
Sorry!
Poor little thing.
Oh, sorry. I was about to
take that out since it wilted.
Oh, it's okay.
Wow, that's amazing.
I just gave it some of my energy.
Are you a witch?
I'm just an apprentice still.
Oh, do you go to that school, then?
I'm actually about to knock
on their door right now.
Welcome.
Oh, hi. My name is Tiara.
Please, come this way.
Um, I wanted to go to this school...
This way, please.
Um... Okay.
Welcome to Flora Girls' Academy.
I'm the school's director, Chloe.
Tiara-san, was it?
Yeah, I... I mean, yes. I was hoping
you'd allow me to study at this school—
Very well.
Huh?
I will allow you to attend this academy.
Um, isn't there an exam, or...?
Well, let's see...
Then if you would take a moment
to touch that stone.
It can tell if you have
what it takes to be a witch or not.
The doors of this academy are open
to all that have a bright future.
Thank you very much!
Give light to the stars,
bless the earth...
—earth...
and give thanks to
the Witch of Dawn, Flora.
Come in.
Pardon me.
Huh? Rose?!
Tiara-sama!
I've missed you!
I missed you so much, Rosetta!
I missed you, too, Tiara-sama.
I heard you were going to this school,
but I didn't think I'd see you so quickly!
Please show Tiara-san around the campus.
As you wish.
Also, please welcome
Tiara-san into your group.
Huh? But that's—
This is not a suggestion.
It has already been decided.
Yes, ma'am.
It's been so long, hasn't it?
The last time we saw each other was...
Two years, three months, and 14 days.
Of course, you'd know that.
What a lovely courtyard.
Yes. It's the perfect place to take a break.
Yeah, it seems like it.
Why did you decide to attend
this academy, Tiara-sama?
Hey, why do you keep speaking so formally to me?
That's because—
We're both students here.
It's weird for you to use "sama."
Not to mention, you're my senior.
But Tiara-sama—
If you're going to keep that up,
I'll just have to call you Rosetta-senpai.
As you wish—Ahem. Oh, all right, Tiara.
Well, let's go.
Oh, what are these groups that
the director was talking about?
A lot of the students here
join groups to help each other out,
since it's a lot harder working on your own.
So I get to be in the same group as you?
Who else is in our group?
I'll introduce you to them right now.
Um, hi. I'm Lynette.
It's a pleasure to meet you!
Likewise.
Are you sure you want to be
in the same group as us?
That was the director's decision.
The director's? That's strange.
That's usually up to the student...
It bit me!
Yes.
What are you doing, Lily?!
Get it off me!
Wow, there are so many books here.
There are! This library is absolutely amazing!
There are people who come from
faraway for the books here!
Ehhh. You must really love books...
I love reading stories oh so much!
These books all seem really difficult to read.
"Now, let us set sail upon
the true ocean called love..."
No! You've got the wrong idea!
Please forget that you ever saw this!
Cast those memories into oblivion!
As you all know, the essence of magic
lies with pyroxenes.
Pyroxenes are the crystallized form
of pyrosand. In order to...
There are all kinds of classes,
but students are free
to choose the ones they want.
Wow, you can choose?
Okay, Champe.
Leave it to me.
Slowly, slowly...
There are plenty of classes and exams
that require groups of people.
So that must be when we work
with our groups.
She's flying!
You can make those discs float
by filling them with mana.
How do you steer them?
It's technically all about balance...
but it's not as easy as it sounds.
What are you doing, Luci?!
Like it's my fault!
You're the one who was zoning out!
There they are.
The other members of our group?
Yes.
Fwoosh!
The blonde girl who just
dodged the ball is Lavie.
The girl who just caught it is Ashley.
Now with you here,
we have five members in our group.
They're both really good.
That's 15 to 7, so game set.
You guys were watching?
Yes.
Wasn't that last super shot just amazing?
That was all thanks to my pass.
Nah, no way. Even Tom
could've pulled off a pass like that.
Now for some introductions.
This is a new student
who'll be joining our group...
I'm Tiara. Nice to meet you.
I'm Ashley.
I'm Lavie, this academy's ace!
Self-proclaimed ace.
Wait, you're joining our group?!
Are you sure?
Yes, I'd love to.
Heck yeah! I love you lots!
That's a relief. You actually seem
astute unlike someone else I know.
Hey, are you talking about me?
And what the heck does astute mean?!
Are you telling me you don't know?
Uh... Of course, I do!
Astute, right? So basically...
So it means... Is it something like a newt?
Are you absolutely positive that you want
to be in the same group as her?
Oh, yeah!
Since we're going to be friends,
I'll introduce you to some of my friends, too,
Tiara-chan!
—chan?!
They're so cute!
I know, right? Their names are Tom and Sherry.
Though they're both female.
Wait, is that weird?
They're the best of friends
since they grew up together.
They're basically childhood friends.
Then they're just like Rosetta and me.
Oh, really?
We hadn't seen each other in forever,
though. It's been two years...
...three months, and 14 days.
You're supposed to hit
as many targets as you can.
That seems like a lot of fun.
Excellent.
Next!
This is a class on metallization magic.
You're too soft! Concentrate!
That seems hard.
So this is the pool.
Yeah. I figured that out.
So close!
That's too bad. All right, next!
They're using magical arrows.
It's harder than it looks.
You need ample mana,
concentration, not to mention,
a strong core and muscles to pull this off.
I don't think I can do it...
Oh, dear. That's minus two points.
Hey, isn't it dangerous being this close?
You don't need to worry about that.
There's a barrier that holds in the flame.
All right, next person.
Ehhh.
So when that arrow hits the target...
Hang on a second. Did you just say flame?
...it's set to explode.
You can basically take out
a magical beast in one blow.
Tiara?
What's the matter, Tiara?! Tiara!
Tia!
ひたすら描いてた虹の色
I kept drawing rainbow colours over and over
hitasura kaiteta niji no iro
もう七色じゃ足りないから
Seven colours are not enough
mou nanairo ja tarinai kara
毎日はすでにいつもを
Everyday leaps over the "usual" and enters a new chapter
mainichi wa sude ni itsumo wo
飛び越えて新章なのさ
tobikoete shinshou nano sa
物語は遥か彼方へ
The story is going beyond
monogatari wa haruka kanata e
心で鳴り出す鐘の音が
The bell toll in my heart
kokoro de naridasu kane no ne ga
少しずつ大きくなってゆく
is getting louder bit by bit
sukoshi zutsu ookiku natte yuku
その高鳴りを信じて
Believe in the excitement
sono takanari wo shinjite
一歩を踏み出せたなら
And take one step forward
ippo wo fumidaseta nara
想像以上のチカラに変わってるよ
It'll give me more power than I ever imagined
souzou ijouno chikara ni kawatteru yo
絶対なんてない
Can't be for sure
zettai nante nai
なにも
Nothing
nanimo
確信はできない
There's no guarantee
kakushin wa dekinai
だれも
No one
daremo
でもあきらめない
But I won't give up
demo akiramenai
だから
That's why
dakara
進んでくことが
I can still move forward
susundeku koto ga
できるよ
I can still move forward
dekiru yo
ここには魔法があるから
Because there's magic right in here
koko ni wa mahou ga aru kara
だって星より輝きだしたのに
It started to be brighter than the stars
datte hoshi yori kagayaki dashita no ni
立ち止まれるはずもないから
I can't stop now
tachidomareru hazu mo nai kara
時代はついに新しい幕開けを迎えたのさ
It entered into a new era
jidai wa tsui ni atarashii makuake wo mukaeta no sa
溢れた想いを輝石に込めて
Placing this overflowing feelings into this gem
afureta omoi wo kiseki ni komete
未来の方へ
And go beyond the future
saki no hou e
Tiara, wait!
I've made up my mind!
No. You mustn't go.
Ugh, forget you, Onee-chan!
Tiara!
Tiara-sama!
Thank goodness you're all right.
Where am I?
This is the academy's lounge.
Are you in any pain?
I'm fine now, Rosetta-senpai.
Sorry, Tiara.
As long as you can take the hint.
Why don't we head to our dorms for the day?
Sure! Lead the way, captain!
But before that, we'll need
to get a certain something.
And what's that?
Your uniform.
I'll go ahead and get it for you,
so you can explore upstairs.
It's so pretty.
After the long winter
nagai fuyu wo koete
長い冬を超えて
The next season brings
yagate kuru kisetsu wa
やがて来る季節は
Birds singing songs
kotori ga saezuri
小鳥が囀り
And flowers smelling so sweet
hana wa kaguwashiku
花は香しく
It all flows towards love
ai e to nagareteiku
愛へと流れていく
Oh, guiding light
michibiku hikari wo
導く光を
Please shine upon us
dou ka bokura wo terashite
どうか僕らを照らして
Please shine upon us
dou ka bokura wo terashite
どうか僕らを照らして
You sound as lovely as ever.
You should've said you were
standing there. How embarrassing.
That takes me back. Wasn't that...
Yeah. It's my sister's song.
I was always so sickly, so she'd always
make me feel better with her songs.
Eliza-sama loves you very much
and was always worried about you.
Yeah... Back then, things were still...
Oh, no. It's nothing.
The reason I'm so much better now
is because of my sister's songs.
I'm sure of it.
Yes.
I'm sure it is.
What a nice breeze.
I guess I fell asleep.
You must've been tired from your long trip.
Yeah, the trip was longer than I'd expected.
Thanks.
Flora-sama!
Is that...
It's the cafeteria.
Then we should grab a bite to eat, too!
—Wait—
—And then I said— Whoa, there!
Tiara!
I'm so sorry!
It's dangerous, running like that.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
What's a Lapis doing here?
Yes, I'm very sorry about that. Let's go.
Huh? We can't be here?
Our rank can't come here until later.
Rank?
Hey, you.
Yes?
That hair accessory...
Oh, this? My big sister gave it to me.
Your sister?
Don't tell me you're...
Huh?
Out of my way.
What's gotten into you, Yue-chin?!
Sorry about that.
Wait up, you two!
Not bad.
Indeed.
You look lovely.
Thanks!
Did you pick a room yet?
Not yet... And this is a four-person room.
I do believe the corner room
nearby is currently vacant.
But that's a room for two.
Well, individual rooms are super popular
and there probably aren't any left, so why not?
But is it okay for me to use
a two-person room on my own?
Good point...
Requesting it might prove difficult.
It wouldn't be fair to leave Tiara-chan all alone...
So it's all up to you...
...Rose-chan!
Me? Wait, are you sure?
Of course.
Do what you can for Tiara-san.
That'll give us more room in here, too.
Then...
I still have a lot to learn,
so it'll be a huge help.
My, my...
Well, don't you seem happy.
It's getting hot in here.
It is?
I'll go ahead and put in a request
so you two can use the room immediately.
I don't think it's that hot in here.
It's scorching hot.
What are you people talking about?!
It all looks so yummy!
Well, let's not wait any longer.
Give light to the stars, bless the earth,
and give thanks to the Witch of Dawn, Flora.
The head chef here is top class.
Apparently, Chloe-sensei scouted them
herself from Marseille.
Well, I don't really care,
as long as the grub's good.
You mean if the food is edible.
You say something?
No, nothing at all.
No, you totally said something.
I did not.
By the way, why weren't we allowed
into the cafeteria earlier?
You did.
I did not.
You totally did!
Well...
Well, we're Lapis, meaning we go last.
Lapis? I guess they did mention
that word earlier...
Wait, inconceivable...
Did you not tell her?
Not yet.
What?!
For real?
Unbelievable.
At this school, we're split into three ranks
depending on our academic scores.
They are Noir, Rouge, and Lapis.
The Noir students always get
to eat and use the bath, first.
Next is Rouge.
Then does that mean...
We're the lowest ranking Lapis!
If you belong to a group, your rank will be
determined from the group total.
It's what you call joke responsibility!
You mean joint.
I see... But if it just means we have to eat
and take baths later, that doesn't seem so...
Yes... Well...
You've got a point, but...
We all received failing grades last term.
And, well... If we fail again this term...
We all get to be expelled together!
Huh?
Huh?!
窓の外は 優しい月明かり そっと
mado no soto wa yasashii tsukiakari sotto
Outside the window, the gentle moonlight is shining softly
灯り消して 夢の橋を渡ろう
akari keshite yume no hashi wo watarou
Put out the lights and cross the bridge of dreams
消えそうで消えないヒカリが今
kie soude kienai hikari ga ima
The weakening yet everlasting light is now
まぶたの向こうの世界に広がった
mabuta no mukou no sekai ni hirogatta
Spreading out into the world behind my eyelids
色んな想いが溢れて
ironna omoi ga afurete
Various feelings are overflowing
キラキラ眩しく輝いてる
kirakira mabushiku kagayaiteru
sparklingly and dazzlingly shining
ずっと
zutto
Forever
It's shining stars
明日はどんな日になるかな
ashita wa donna hi ni naru kana
I wonder what kind of day tomorrow will be
心に映し出す景色は
kokoro ni utsushidasu keshiki wa
The scenery that is reflected in my heart
期待 涙 夢の 全部が重なった
kitai namida yume no zenbu ga kasanatta
Expectations, tears, and dreams, all of it bottled up in my heart
私のプラネタリウム
watashi no planetarium
My planetarium
ほら
hora
Look, in that star that is shining the brightest
一番輝いている あの星に
ichiban kagayaiteiru ano hoshi ni
願いかけて「おやすみ」
negai kakete oyasumi
A wish is enclosed: "Good night"