To think I might be facing expulsion
as soon as I got to this school...
I'm sorry I didn't say anything sooner.
You really shouldn't be in our group.
Why would a princess like yo—
No formalities. Forget I'm a princess.
I don't want everyone to be uptight around me.
But...
Please.
All right.
Thank you.
Anyway, we won't be expelled
as long as we get points, right?
Yes. As long as we're able to gain points
necessary from our grades from
our classes, tests, as well as
extracurricular activities.
I see.
But you shouldn't think about it too much.
Let's turn in for the night.
Yeah, you're right.
Good night.
I'm going to turn off the lights.
Oh, sure.
ひたすら描いてた虹の色
I kept drawing rainbow colours over and over
hitasura kaiteta niji no iro
もう七色じゃ足りないから
Seven colours are not enough
mou nanairo ja tarinai kara
毎日はすでにいつもを
Everyday leaps over the "usual" and enters a new chapter
mainichi wa sude ni itsumo wo
飛び越えて新章なのさ
tobikoete shinshou nano sa
物語は遥か彼方へ
The story is going beyond
monogatari wa haruka kanata e
心で鳴り出す鐘の音が
The bell toll in my heart
kokoro de naridasu kane no ne ga
少しずつ大きくなってゆく
is getting louder bit by bit
sukoshi zutsu ookiku natte yuku
その高鳴りを信じて
Believe in the excitement
sono takanari wo shinjite
一歩を踏み出せたなら
And take one step forward
ippo wo fumidaseta nara
想像以上のチカラに変わってるよ
It'll give me more power than I ever imagined
souzou ijouno chikara ni kawatteru yo
絶対なんてない
Can't be for sure
zettai nante nai
なにも
Nothing
nanimo
確信はできない
There's no guarantee
kakushin wa dekinai
だれも
No one
daremo
でもあきらめない
But I won't give up
demo akiramenai
だから
That's why
dakara
進んでくことが
I can still move forward
susundeku koto ga
できるよ
I can still move forward
dekiru yo
ここには魔法があるから
Because there's magic right in here
koko ni wa mahou ga aru kara
だって星より輝きだしたのに
It started to be brighter than the stars
datte hoshi yori kagayaki dashita no ni
立ち止まれるはずもないから
I can't stop now
tachidomareru hazu mo nai kara
時代はついに新しい幕開けを迎えたのさ
It entered into a new era
jidai wa tsui ni atarashii makuake wo mukaeta no sa
溢れた想いを輝石に込めて
Placing this overflowing feelings into this gem
afureta omoi wo kiseki ni komete
未来の方へ
And go beyond the future
saki no hou e
Good morning!
Rise and shine! Time to get up!
Tiara-san?
Rosetta filled me in on everything!
Come on, let's go get those points!
The creation of this academy is
a big part of Waleland's history.
Two hundred years ago,
a giant magical beast attacked,
and the world was gripped with fear.
The great witch Flora...
She's sure motivated.
She said that she was going
to hold a study group after school.
What?!
Lavie-san, shh!
No way! I'm not going to
study after school, too!
You there!
Ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Silence, please. Minus three points.
You've got this, Ashley!
We'll get points as long as
you shoot right in the middle!
Um, Tiara... You may be interfering
with her concentration...
Don't worry! I'm sure you can
do it as long as you concentrate!
And there goes some points.
Lower your back a little more, Lyn-chan!
Lavie's really good!
She's great at sports, at least.
Okay, my turn.
Don't push yourself too much.
Yeah, I know.
Is Tiara good at sports?
She used to be sick all the time,
so she wasn't really active.
So if I had to choose...
So she's not...
Tiara!
I guess it broke...
Minus ten points.
I see.
Rather than going all out
for our classes and losing points,
we need a good way of getting points.
Correct...
I can't believe you
figured it out already. Good job!
But this is easier said than done...
Things like that happen...
Or we go too far...
They're ready to take points
from us at any turn.
Though in your case, most of your problems
would be solved if you'd just study.
But I'm getting points other ways!
I know it was Chloe-sensei's orders,
but maybe you should ask to be
put in another group, Tiara-san.
No, I really like this group.
Is it because Rosetta's in this group?
There's that, but it's fun
being with all of you.
So I just want to be with you guys.
You're making us blush.
Rosetta sure is taking a while.
Oh, Rosetta-san said she had something to do.
Huh?
She does have a habit
of disappearing at night.
I heard that there were
extracurricular activities, so maybe it's that?
No, I'm pretty sure Rosetta
doesn't belong to any club.
I thought that she was
just shopping or something.
She does do it quite often.
I wonder what it is...
It couldn't be...
A girl who frequently sneaks off campus
as soon as the sun sets...
I smell a mys—
Could she secretly be meeting with someone?!
Meating?! You mean Rose's
secretly having a hamburger?!
Not that kind of meat.
What other kind is there?
What I'm saying is that it's not that kind of meat...
But Rosetta would never
do something like that...
The point is that we're going to
have to look into this further!
I'm going to head out for a bit.
Yeah, okay. Take all the time you need.
Take all the time I need?
Oh, it's nothing...
Have a good time.
Thanks.
What do you lot think you're doing?
Shh!
What are you, ninjas?
Things are getting really exciting!
My heart's about to burst through my chest.
What was that for—?!
Shh!
That's...
Yes.
Is something the matter?
Oh, it's nothing.
So that's who she's meeting with...
But she's a girl...
That doesn't matter!
The more responsible someone may seem,
the amount of stress they have to deal with
leads them to search for extreme forms of love!
You seem to know a lot about this.
This happens all the time in stories and—
Hey, she's gone!
Huh?!
Looks like they're just acquaintances.
She's totally gone!
Sorry, this is all my fault.
No, I lost sight of her, too.
Yup. It's all Ashley's fault.
Hey.
Welcome! Oh. Hey, wait.
Ratura.
It's rare to see you here.
Yeah.
You gonna give us something on the house?
Don't get your hopes up too much.
Aw...
You guys know her?
Oh, let me introduce you.
This is Ratura-san.
She's in the Lapis rank, just like us.
I'm Tiara. I just transferred to the academy.
Oh, so that's why I haven't
seen you around before.
I'm Ratura. Pleased to meet ya.
Thanks for waiting. Here's your
pale ale and your pescatore.
You're as cute as ever, Ratura-chan.
Well, duh!
I guess she's studying to be
a witch and working part time.
Apparently, Ratura-san comes
from a rich family,
but she has very strict parents.
She's always saying she doesn't
have enough spending money.
So that's why she's working...
I've never worked before,
but it must be really hard.
It seems like she enjoys it, though.
Perhaps... Rosetta-san is working, too.
That's hard to imagine.
Because she's a noble?
You knew?
You can tell just by looking at her.
My father is the captain
of the Dordtgard knights.
And because of that,
I've encountered a lot of nobles and royalty,
so I could tell.
You psychic, or something?
It just means that she's very observant.
You're a noble, too, aren't you, Tiara?
Huh?! Yeah, uh... Something like that.
I knew it.
Wow...
Thanks for waiting.
Yay!
When did you even order that?
Well, I was hungry!
You won't be able to eat dinner, then.
I have a separate stomach for that!
By the way, Ratura-san,
have you seen Rosetta-san?
Yeah, I just saw her.
Where?! Where was she?!
Huh...? Behind the shop.
Huh?
No, no, no!
My precious Hamburg steak!
According to Ratura-san,
she should be around here...
My Hamburg steak...
I'll treat you next time, okay?
Really?!
Yup! It's a promise!
Yay!
She knows what she's about.
That's...
R-Rosetta?
Rose-chan is...
...dumpster diving?
Huh?
Dumpster diving?
Wait! You've got the wrong idea!
I was just looking for Alfred.
Alfred...?
That must be who she's meeting with.
Meeting?
Huh?
You were looking for a duck that escaped?!
I've actually been working multiple
part-time jobs. I'm a pet sitter today.
But why are you working?
Well...
Oh, hey. I think I saw it earlier—
that duck of yours.
Wait, where?!
Right in front of the café over there.
Thanks!
Wait! We'll help!
No! I can't let you
do anything like that, Tiara!
But...
I'll be fine on my own.
You guys can head back to the academy.
Rosetta!
Ashley?
It's like the old Rosetta-san...
What do you mean?
Rosetta used to bury herself in her studies.
She tried way too hard to get
good grades and it just backfired.
And because of that, she ended up
clashing with other students...
I thought we were finally able to
help each other out
when we joined the same group.
I want to help you, Rosetta-san!
Lynette...
Well, you show me your homework all the time.
Lavie...
Friends should always help each other out.
Ashley...
Rosetta.
Okay.
Thank you, everyone.
I guess that settles it.
Yeah!
Leave it to us.
We'll find him in no time if we work together.
Where do ducks like to go?
Let's split up.
Good idea.
So, why did you start working?
Well... So...
Two years ago, my family ran into
some trouble, and our savings ran dry.
What?!
But it's okay.
We still have our titles as nobles,
but we're making enough to get by.
But...
I think our family prefers
to live without constraints,
and I really don't have any problems with it.
I'm having a lot of fun now,
so don't worry about it, okay?
Okay... I understand. But if there's
ever anything troubling you,
don't hesitate to tell me, okay?
It's a promise.
Yes, I promise.
We still haven't found it.
Maybe there isn't a duck after all.
But you saw it, didn't you?
Oh, yeah.
Uh, hey...
There it is!
Let's catch it!
Hold it right there, Alfred!
You're way too fast...
Let's surround it!
Got it!
Lynette, this way!
Okay...
Where could've Alfred run off to...?
This takes me back.
Huh?
Remember when you sneaked me out of
the castle when we were little?
Jeez! Hold it!
Tia!
And then I took a tumble...
Pain, pain, go away!
Look, all better! This owie's all better!
You're okay now. I cast a spell
so it won't hurt anymore.
Yeah! Thanks, Rose!
I'm sorry for letting you get hurt back then.
I was happy, though.
Because we got to play together in the town.
Tiara...
Ugh, why are you so fast?!
Perfect! Ashley and Lynette are over there!
Griffin Workshop's newest creation!
How cute are you?!
Ashley!
Sorry! I couldn't help myself!
Damn it! In that case, Lyn-chan...
Unbelievable! This magical tome is so rare!
I must buy it
Lyn-chan...?
Oh hi, Rosetta.
This is really good.
And, it was on the house.
Would you like one, too, little lady?
Maybe next time. By the way,
did you happen to see a duck?
Huh? A duck?
Hold it right there, Alflex!
Tiara!
Got it!
Please wait...
I wonder what all that's about.
No idea.
We've got you now, Alford!
On the count of three, we'll all grab him!
Okay.
One, two...
Hold it.
Are we going to jump him
while you say three,
or jump him right after you say three?
Which is it?
As I say it, obviously.
Wait, it's not after?
That doesn't matter! Just hurry!
Okay, let's just go!
One, two, three!
Tia!
Are you okay?
Yeah, thanks...
Wait! Where's Alfred?!
Leave this to me!
I found something that should work...
There it is!
I am the child of Isabelle.
Story 73. Bind them!
I did it!
Thank you all for your help today.
I'm glad we could help.
Now we can relax.
We'll go return Alfred, so you two
should return to the dorms to change.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
We might catch a cold otherwise!
Can a dummy like you even get sick?
Whaddya just say?!
May I head back, as well?
I want to read this so badly
that I can barely contain myself.
Yes, of course.
Say.
You called me earlier, didn't you?
You called me "Tia."
Oh! I just panicked, and—
It was like the good old days.
Yeah.
Um... If you don't mind,
may I keep calling you Tia?
Of course, Rose!
Oh, right. Tonight's...
Tia, come with me!
This way.
Is something wrong?
We can probably see them from here.
What's about to start?
An Orchestra.
This city, Malmcester,
is supported by mana.
An Orchestra gathers people's feelings
and accumulates them into mana.
Orchestra?
Aren't those people...
They're supernova.
Millefeuille, Fiona,
and Yue.
Apparently, she's the princess of Ryuto.
The princess of Ryuto...
絶望を照らした一筋の
zetsubou wo terashita hitosuji no
A ray of light that illuminated my despair
強い光に目を奪われた
tsuyoi hikari ni me wo ubawareta
I was blinded by the powerful light
いつか自分もこの宇宙で
itsuka jibun mo kono uchuu de
Someday I, myself too, in this universe
強く強く光る星になる
tsuyoku tsuyoku hikaru hoshi ni naru
Will become a powerful, powerful star
Wow...
I wonder if my sister
was singing like this, too.
yah yah yah
Tia, is the reason you joined this academy...
まっすぐな閃光
massugu na senkou
A straight flash of light
yah yah yah
Yeah. I wanted to be like my sister.
まっすぐな羨望
massugu na senbou
A straightforward jealousy
yah yah yah
まっすぐな感情を
massugu na kanjou wo
A straightforward emotion
乗せ叫んだ
nose sakenda
Yelled out loud
今わただ アオノショウドウ
ima wa tada ao no shoudou
Right now it is just a Blue Impulse
誰にも負けらんない レゾリューション
dare ni mo makerannai resolution
A resolution that won't be beaten by anyone
たとえこの身 果てても
tatoe kono mi hatete mo
And even if this body perishes
譲れない想い
yuzurenai omoi
I can't give up
yah yah yah
まっすぐな閃光
massugu na senkou
A straight flash of light
yah yah yah
まっすぐな羨望
massugu na senbou
A straightforward jealousy
yah yah yah
もうじき世界が
moujiki sekai ga
Before long the world will start to move with this
動き出すような 衝動
ugokidasu youna shoudou
So this is an Orchestra...
窓の外は 優しい月明かり そっと
mado no soto wa yasashii tsukiakari sotto
Outside the window, the gentle moonlight is shining softly
灯り消して 夢の橋を渡ろう
akari keshite yume no hashi wo watarou
Put out the lights and cross the bridge of dreams
消えそうで消えないヒカリが今
kie soude kienai hikari ga ima
The weakening yet everlasting light is now
まぶたの向こうの世界に広がった
mabuta no mukou no sekai ni hirogatta
Spreading out into the world behind my eyelids
色んな想いが溢れて
ironna omoi ga afurete
Various feelings are overflowing
キラキラ眩しく輝いてる
kirakira mabushiku kagayaiteru
sparklingly and dazzlingly shining
ずっと
zutto
Forever
It's shining stars
明日はどんな日になるかな
ashita wa donna hi ni naru kana
I wonder what kind of day tomorrow will be
心に映し出す景色は
kokoro ni utsushidasu keshiki wa
The scenery that is reflected in my heart
期待 涙 夢の 全部が重なった
kitai namida yume no zenbu ga kasanatta
Expectations, tears, and dreams, all of it bottled up in my heart
私のプラネタリウム
watashi no planetarium
My planetarium
ほら
hora
Look, in that star that is shining the brightest
一番輝いている あの星に
ichiban kagayaiteiru ano hoshi ni
願いかけて「おやすみ」
negai kakete oyasumi
A wish is enclosed: "Good night"