I guess you're our first targets.
Let's get this over with.
What?! I'm the one who's gonna win!
You've got this, team!
Lucifer and Angelica... Not good.
Are they strong?
From what I heard, very.
But they always skip class,
so I don't have further details.
I'm taking you out first, Lavie!
Ow...
Oh-ho... Not bad.
Right back at ya!
Not bad at... all!
Coco!
One to zero!
I'll take it easy on you.
I won't use any magic.
ひたすら描いてた虹の色
I kept drawing rainbow colours over and over
hitasura kaiteta niji no iro
もう七色じゃ足りないから
Seven colours are not enough
mou nanairo ja tarinai kara
毎日はすでにいつもを
Everyday leaps over the "usual" and enters a new chapter
mainichi wa sude ni itsumo wo
飛び越えて新章なのさ
tobikoete shinshou nano sa
物語は遥か彼方へ
The story is going beyond
monogatari wa haruka kanata e
心で鳴り出す鐘の音が
The bell toll in my heart
kokoro de naridasu kane no ne ga
少しずつ大きくなってゆく
is getting louder bit by bit
sukoshi zutsu ookiku natte yuku
その高鳴りを信じて
Believe in the excitement
sono takanari wo shinjite
一歩を踏み出せたなら
And take one step forward
ippo wo fumidaseta nara
想像以上のチカラに変わってるよ
It'll give me more power than I ever imagined
souzou ijouno chikara ni kawatteru yo
絶対なんてない
Can't be for sure
zettai nante nai
なにも
Nothing
nanimo
確信はできない
There's no guarantee
kakushin wa dekinai
だれも
No one
daremo
でもあきらめない
But I won't give up
demo akiramenai
だから
That's why
dakara
進んでくことが
I can still move forward
susundeku koto ga
できるよ
I can still move forward
dekiru yo
ここには魔法があるから
Because there's magic right in here
koko ni wa mahou ga aru kara
だって星より輝きだしたのに
It started to be brighter than the stars
datte hoshi yori kagayaki dashita no ni
立ち止まれるはずもないから
I can't stop now
tachidomareru hazu mo nai kara
時代はついに新しい幕開けを迎えたのさ
It entered into a new era
jidai wa tsui ni atarashii makuake wo mukaeta no sa
溢れた想いを輝石に込めて
Placing this overflowing feelings into this gem
afureta omoi wo kiseki ni komete
未来の方へ
And go beyond the future
saki no hou e
You seem rather chipper today, Lavie-san.
Oh? You think so? I mean, I'm not that chipper.
All right, all done.
Here you go, Lynette.
Thank you so much!
It's lovely!
I'm glad you like it.
Ashley...?
What about mine?
Oh, I'll make yours another time.
Another... time?
There!
So if you hit someone with
the ball like that, you get a point.
Yes. And the team to get 15 points first wins.
Whoever gets hit will trade
with someone in the outfield.
Sorry!
Those are the basic rules to bumpball.
It's okay.
This is a league tournament divided into blocks,
so there are probably five matches.
And if we win our block...
We'll get 60 points.
We'll just have to do our best!
Are you allowed to use magic?
You're allowed to use one kind.
One, huh? In that case...
Heya!
So you were watching our game.
Melissa! And, uh...
I'm Lily.
And I'm Coco.
You should know that by now, jeez.
Sorry about that.
You're going to be on our team
the next tournament, right?
Yes. We look forward to it.
And you guys have Lavie and Ashley, too!
That means we're totally set!
Ashley, you jerk!
Why are you so mad?
I made you a bag the other day!
Never mind!
Lavie-san!
Lavie?
What happened?
I can't say that I'm entirely sure myself.
Ashley-san made me a tote bag, but...
Ashley, you nincompoop.
You dunce.
Coco!
One to zero!
I'll take it easy on you.
I won't use any magic.
Is something going on with those two?
Yeah! Now we're tied!
You shouldn't get so cocky over one point!
What's the big idea?!
Well, you should pay more attention!
Look out!
This is all your fault, Ashley!
Stop blaming other people!
Damn it...
Take that!
Eight to one!
I'm counting on you.
Leave it to me!
The game's just getting started!
Ugh, what is Ashley even doing?
At this rate...
Lavie.
I need you to do the thing.
The thing, eh? You got it!
Yeah, yeah! Rose-chan!
Go, fight! Go, fight, Rose-chan!
You're amazing, you're amazing, Rose-chan!
Lynette, the ball, please.
—Oh, right.
—That's Lavie's...
Physical reinforcement magic.
Two to eight!
What the hell are you doing?!
What the heck was I
supposed to do with that ball?!
Take this!
What?!
There!
One more!
Angelica.
You owe me one.
Rosetta?
Wait, did the spell wear off already?
This is for Rose-chan!
Hup. Luci!
Got it! Take that!
Lily-san!
I'll be okay!
Coco!
Wait, that's not Lily?
That's Lily's magic. She can switch places
with Coco in a mere instant.
What even is the point in that?
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry, Coco!
No... I should really catch on by now...
Coco!
For crying out loud...
Without using Echo Gift? Amazing...
Coco! Thank goodness!
Th-Thank you very much.
You don't need to thank me.
Healing an enemy's wounds? You softie.
That's because you keep
injuring people, Shrimpy Luci!
What'd you call me?!
There!
Oh, my bad. My hand slipped.
You totally did that on purpose!
Excuse me... Please calm down, you two.
What?!
We'll settle this after the match!
Sounds good to me!
Take that!
Fifteen to three! Game set!
All right, let's settle this once and for all!
Bring it on! Step outside!
We already are outside!
Sorry...
You just kept letting them hit you.
What?! You were also—
Hey, it's okay, you two.
We still have four matches left.
We can still turn things around!
Oh, Lavie.
Your uniform...
Oh, yeah. Eh, this is fine.
Wait, but if you keep playing like that...
Nothing to worry about!
All right! Let's take a break
to prepare for the next match!
Lavie.
Take it off.
Huh?
Huh?!
Wait, does that mean that you're—
Wait, no! That's not what...
Ugh, just come with me!
A-Ashley, wait! That hurts!
You're hurting me, dang it!
You didn't have to...
I couldn't just leave you like that.
Okay, all done.
It's cute.
Why are you so angry?
It doesn't matter now. You gave me something.
Gave you something?
Wait—
Yeah.
Happy birthday!
Thanks. I'll take good care of it.
I'll get you a gift for
your birthday, too, Lavie.
Just you wait.
I'm so sorry!
Don't worry about it. You gave me this.
That's not enough!
I know! I'll make you some clothes!
Wait, clothes?
Some really cute clothes!
Like, super cute clothes?
Yeah.
Then I forgive you. Don't forget again, okay?
I promise.
Good.
Are you okay?
The other two are back.
And then... Also...
Looks like they made up.
The game's just begun!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
Fifteen to seven!
Fifteen to five!
There!
Fifteen to eight!
Now we're three-one.
I'm better now, too. I can play.
If we win the next one,
we might be able to win the whole thing.
All right, let's win this thing!
It'll be a piece of cake for us!
Like it's going to be that easy.
Ra-chan!
Champe and Maryberry, too.
What brings you here?
We're four-zero right now!
We're gonna win it all!
Easy peasy!
What's peasy mean?
I dunno.
Ratura aside...
We're definitely not losing to the other two!
Well, we've got Emilia's group on our team.
What?!
You called?
My lady, that is the team we are facing next.
I see. Well, do your best.
Let's have tons of fun!
Regardless, we are going to win.
Seriously?
We've got our work cut out for us.
Are they strong?
Those who are not quite human...
Those three are demi-humans.
Emilia, Alpha, and Salsa.
They're in the top rank, Noir.
Noir...
Be especially careful of Emilia.
You may experience
Energy Drain if she touches you.
Energy Drain?
She'll drain your lifeforce.
Emilia doesn't seem to have control over it.
Huh...
It's amazing that you're playing
with people from Noir.
Right?
Though they just told us they
only needed us to make a team.
We're just for show...
But if you're undefeated,
then you must've beaten Lucifer's team.
We didn't see those two.
What?
I'm sure they're just skipping again as usual.
So they're still fighting...
Stand by!
Let's have a good game!
With our height difference...
Where are you throwing... Wha?!
One to zero!
Damn it! We're counting on you, Lyn-chan!
Okay, I'll do my best.
Great throw!
Okay, here I go!
This is, uh...
I could stop that with like ten pinkies...
That throw was insane!
I can't believe she stopped that.
Alpha-san is a magidoll.
Calculations complete.
Two to zero.
Sorry.
Leave it to me!
Okay!
Take that!
Whoa.
You still have a lot to learn.
Yes!
My, my.
I guess grass wasn't enough to stop it.
Tiara-san!
Behind you! Behind you!
Ow!
Don't sweat it, Tia-chan!
If grass won't work...
Take that!
O Earth, hear the resonance from the ritual!
I am depicted in blood: Sorcier's Legacy.
Erect a mighty wall!
Four to zero!
This isn't good...
I have an idea.
All right.
Here I come, Salsa! My newest throw!
Hey, a flying pig!
Ooh, where? Where?!
You're wide open!
Yeah!
Well done!
No fair, Lavie!
Salsa, you're at fault
for letting your guard down.
Salsa-sama, let us switch.
Boo...
Salsa!
Okay, I'm gonna get you back for that!
That really is scary...
In that case...
Honour the name of the witch of this ritual
and dance, servant!
One sheep... Two sheep... Fwee sheep...
Fwour...
Sheep...
She's asleep.
Yeah, she sure is.
You are only allowed to use one kind of magic.
Huh? But I'm just using this one magical tome.
Then just use one kind of spell
from the magical tome.
I will only allow the wall you erected first.
But...
As a penalty, the opposing team
gets three extra points.
The score is now seven to one.
Leave this to me!
Woo-hoo! Lucky us!
Hey, Ashley.
We... actually have a chance!
Heck yeah, we do!
Fourteen to thirteen!
Yeah! We turned things around!
Now we're at match point!
Just one more point.
Do not hold back, Alpha.
As you wish, my lady.
What?!
That's... Freedom Hand.
Wouldn't that be "hair" since it's her hair?
I guess.
I'd like you to refrain from giving this
a silly name. Also, you lack creativity.
Is that even fair?
Deuce. Fourteen to fourteen.
Be careful.
Yeah.
This isn't good.
It all comes down to this.
Give it to me!
You took far too long to wake up.
I'll show you my full power!
Let's do this, Ashley!
All right.
Lavie! Ashley!
Stand your ground!
It's over!
Wow!
Lynette, Wonderful!
That's amazing!
Leave the rest to me!
We're counting on you!
There!
How naïve.
I'm not done yet!
Fifteen to fourteen!
We did it! We did it, we did it!
Nice throw, Tia-chan!
Well done!
Now we're four-one.
Huh? Dodge, Tiara!
Huh? Ow!
Deuce. Fifteen to fifteen.
Wait, why? Didn't we already win?
It's a deuce.
Deuce?
When both teams hit match point, no one wins
until one team gets two points ahead.
What?!
No way!
Aw, no fair...
It was really close.
Noirs are definitely strong.
But we managed to place third.
All thanks to the ace!
I never got to move around
that much, so I had fun.
Not to mention, we won 30 points—
Great job, Tiara-san.
That last throw was excellent.
Everyone did really great.
Let's win the whole thing next time!
Yeah!
We did it!
We were sorta just there,
but with these points we just won...
We might able to go up a rank to Rouge!
Right, Mar?
Huh?!
Um, yes, maybe...
I hope you don't mind us joining you.
Why are you here? You're Noirs.
It's still the Lapis rank's turn...
Noirs don't need to hold back.
We are not breaking any rules.
Tiara, was it?
Yes.
You're the only one to ever get a point from me.
No one has taken a point from me,
but the match was somewhat delightful.
Today was a lot of fun!
We had fun, too. Thanks.
I guess I wouldn't mind having
another match with you someday.
Yeah! And we won't lose next time!
Huh?
If you touch me...
...my Energy Drain will...
Tia!
Tia! Tia!
Are you all right, Tiara-san?
Tia-chan, you alive?
Wake up! Get a hold of yourself!
窓の外は 優しい月明かり そっと
mado no soto wa yasashii tsukiakari sotto
Outside the window, the gentle moonlight is shining softly
灯り消して 夢の橋を渡ろう
akari keshite yume no hashi wo watarou
Put out the lights and cross the bridge of dreams
消えそうで消えないヒカリが今
kie soude kienai hikari ga ima
The weakening yet everlasting light is now
まぶたの向こうの世界に広がった
mabuta no mukou no sekai ni hirogatta
Spreading out into the world behind my eyelids
色んな想いが溢れて
ironna omoi ga afurete
Various feelings are overflowing
キラキラ眩しく輝いてる
kirakira mabushiku kagayaiteru
sparklingly and dazzlingly shining
ずっと
zutto
Forever
It's shining stars
明日はどんな日になるかな
ashita wa donna hi ni naru kana
I wonder what kind of day tomorrow will be
心に映し出す景色は
kokoro ni utsushidasu keshiki wa
The scenery that is reflected in my heart
期待 涙 夢の 全部が重なった
kitai namida yume no zenbu ga kasanatta
Expectations, tears, and dreams, all of it bottled up in my heart
私のプラネタリウム
watashi no planetarium
My planetarium
ほら
hora
Look, in that star that is shining the brightest
一番輝いている あの星に
ichiban kagayaiteiru ano hoshi ni
願いかけて「おやすみ」
negai kakete oyasumi
A wish is enclosed: "Good night"