Nadeshiko.
We'll be landing in Waleland momentarily.
Finally...
How's Kaede?
I will not give up.
I will persuade Kaede no matter what.
Rock 'n' ro!
ひたすら描いてた虹の色
I kept drawing rainbow colours over and over
hitasura kaiteta niji no iro
もう七色じゃ足りないから
Seven colours are not enough
mou nanairo ja tarinai kara
毎日はすでにいつもを
Everyday leaps over the "usual" and enters a new chapter
mainichi wa sude ni itsumo wo
飛び越えて新章なのさ
tobikoete shinshou nano sa
物語は遥か彼方へ
The story is going beyond
monogatari wa haruka kanata e
心で鳴り出す鐘の音が
The bell toll in my heart
kokoro de naridasu kane no ne ga
少しずつ大きくなってゆく
is getting louder bit by bit
sukoshi zutsu ookiku natte yuku
その高鳴りを信じて
Believe in the excitement
sono takanari wo shinjite
一歩を踏み出せたなら
And take one step forward
ippo wo fumidaseta nara
想像以上のチカラに変わってるよ
It'll give me more power than I ever imagined
souzou ijouno chikara ni kawatteru yo
絶対なんてない
Can't be for sure
zettai nante nai
なにも
Nothing
nanimo
確信はできない
There's no guarantee
kakushin wa dekinai
だれも
No one
daremo
でもあきらめない
But I won't give up
demo akiramenai
だから
That's why
dakara
進んでくことが
I can still move forward
susundeku koto ga
できるよ
I can still move forward
dekiru yo
ここには魔法があるから
Because there's magic right in here
koko ni wa mahou ga aru kara
だって星より輝きだしたのに
It started to be brighter than the stars
datte hoshi yori kagayaki dashita no ni
立ち止まれるはずもないから
I can't stop now
tachidomareru hazu mo nai kara
時代はついに新しい幕開けを迎えたのさ
It entered into a new era
jidai wa tsui ni atarashii makuake wo mukaeta no sa
溢れた想いを輝石に込めて
Placing this overflowing feelings into this gem
afureta omoi wo kiseki ni komete
未来の方へ
And go beyond the future
saki no hou e
So many interesting things!
What do you think?
They look great on you!
Do they have any kind of magic?
These... apparently have analyzing abilities.
You're 156 finches tall,
you weigh 45 stones,
Your bust is eighty...
Rose, wait!
I'm kidding.
Ugh, forget you!
Hello.
Oh!
You're Yue-san from supernova!
I saw your Orchestra the other day!
It was absolutely wonderful!
Getting a compliment from you
doesn't exactly make me happy.
Um... Do you have any advice
for bettering our grades? We're—
Your group is on the brink
of getting expelled, isn't it?
Huh?
Don't you feel bad for Eliza-sama,
being such a disgrace?
Are you all right?
That was out of nowhere,
so I was a bit shocked.
But it's hard to believe
Yue-san would say things like that.
Do you two know each other?
No... But it looks like she knows me.
Apparently so.
Oh?
Do you know her?
That's Kaede.
She's an exchange student from Yamato.
Welcome back!
Rosetta-san!
When did you get back?
Just a moment ago. Um... May I ask who that is?
She's a new student.
I'm Tiara!
It's nice to meet you. I'm Kaede.
Pleasure to meet you.
Likewise.
What kind of shop is this?
They sell divination items here.
Kaede belongs to the Divination Club.
Ah...
Come to think of it,
you're not in a club yet, Tia.
Really? Then would you like to join mine?
You're not in a club either, are you, Rose?
Well, I have work.
But if you're planning to join one,
you should really give it some thought.
Yes... You should really give it some thought.
Is something wrong?
Well, Nadeshiko...
Kaede!
You went too far ahead. Oh?
Welcome back, Nadeshiko.
This is a new student at our school, Tiara.
Oh, I see.
I'm Kaede's older sister
Nadeshiko. Rock 'n' ro!
Rock 'n' ro?
I absolutely love rock and roll.
Please stop being so weird
towards someone you just met.
Kaede!
Well, I hope to see you at school soon!
Uh... sure.
Why aren't you changing, Lavie?
No reason. Just because.
Your uniform will wrinkle if you sleep in them.
Well, that's not good.
I'm gonna go change!
I wonder what's gotten into her.
Oh? Tsubaki-san?
Good evening.
You're back.
It's been a while.
You all seem well.
Are you Tiara?
Yes.
I'm the oldest of the three sisters, Tsubaki.
Three sisters?
She's Nadeshiko and Kaede's older sister.
It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance.
Were you able to get out of your rut?
Well, we did have a breakthrough, but...
Tsubaki and her sisters also perform Orchestras.
You mean just like supernova?
Yes, exactly. But we haven't been
able to wow the crowd lately...
I heard that you went on
a journey to find yourselves!
We just went back home for a while.
But that's where Nadeshiko
discovered something new for us.
But Kaede refuses to join in.
I'm trying to get them to reconcile, but...
I heard that you're trying
to figure out what club to join.
Huh? Yes...?
Then would you mind helping me out a bit?
Observing various clubs?
Really?
Yes. I want you two to help her out.
Us?
You want them to go with you, don't you?
Um... I'm very interested in
divination and rock...
Really?!
And I was curious about a lot of other things...
Of course!
Let's go right away!
I'm counting on you girls.
You're not coming with us, Tsubaki?
Unfortunately, I'm a bit busy.
I'd go with you girls if I could.
You must care a lot about your sisters.
That's not... exactly the case.
She's just a weirdo with
an extreme sister complex.
That's so mean! I'm just ever
so worried about my little sisters...
These are mine!
Aw...
That's okay. I have another.
And over here, I have Nadeshiko's.
Tsubaki?!
Give that back!
What do you think you're doing?!
Tsubaki!
I must say... I rather enjoy watching
my little sisters act so... desperately.
Give that back!
I guess there are all kinds of divination.
Would you like me to tell your fortune?
Her divination is spot on!
Kaede is an absolute divination fanatic.
Like you can talk...
Let's rock!
You've surpassed being a fanatic
and you're just a weirdo.
Did I do anything weird?
Welcome to MIT!
MIT?
The Magic Item Invention Team.
Enjoy your stay.
Is that a magic item, too?
That board is able to relay
the owner's thoughts and feelings vocally.
Mary-san made it herself!
It's even on the market!
It's called a Berry Board!
It's not very popular for some reason though...
Well, you know...
We don't actually need it.
All right!
Now, strip!
Hiyah!
Yes!
It's my turn now. Die!
Welcome to the Cabaret, Onee-sama!
Okay, say, "Ah."
Cabaret?
This is the Cabaret Club...
It's so lovely!
Is this... Shiny Sand?
Yes, it is.
Plants grow better when
there's Shiny Sand in the soil.
You know a lot about this, Tiara. Well done.
Um, is this...?
Yes, it's a Shiny Stone ore.
We shatter that and mix it into the soil.
I think I can use this in my divination.
I got it in the forest northeast from here.
Apparently, there are
even bigger ones further in...
I'd love to get some!
Absolutely not! There are Magical Monsters
that appear around there.
But...
No means no!
This doesn't concern you, Nadeshiko.
Kaede...
So... What other kinds of flowers do you have?
Well, for rarer breeds, we have geraniums.
Really?!
Wow! That's amazing! I've never
seen the real thing before!
So where should we go next?
Actually, I'm sure we've seen enough.
Huh?
You seemed to really enjoy Gardening Club.
Was I that obvious?
I really love flowers!
After seeing everyone so passionate
about their clubs, it just made me realize
just how much I love rock!
And that I can't wait to sing
my perfection of rock!
You already have a new song?
I even have the choreography figured out!
Then do whatever you want.
Do whatever kind of music
you want with Tsubaki!
Kaede!
I'll go after her!
I'm sorry for the sudden intrusion.
Don't even worry about it.
Let's sleep together tonight.
Okay.
You can talk to me if there's
anything troubling you, okay?
Tiara-san...
Will you be my older sister?
Huh?!
Absolutely not!
Why'd you answer?
I, uh... Never mind.
I'm sorry. You just seem
so reliable, so I just...
Tsubaki and Nadeshiko
seem like reliable sisters, too.
They're both just weirdos.
And I just don't understand
why we have to do new music.
We've worked so hard together
up until this point...
Yet they want to change our direction
because we aren't getting enough attention...
What are they even thinking?
I actually have an older sister
that's a witch, too.
You do?
Yes. But my sister was very
against me going to this academy.
She was?
Actually... I fought with her
right before I came here, too.
I'm pretty sure she didn't like the idea of me
becoming a witch after I was sick for so long.
But...
But I want to be an amazing witch
just like my sister.
That's what I decided.
I think that's going to give me
the courage to face my sister head on.
Courage...
You're up early.
Tiara-san.
You can stay here until
you've gathered your thoughts.
Thank you very much.
But I...
Kaede!
Tsubaki.
Is something wrong?
When I woke up, I found this.
"I'm going to the forest."
Wait, is this...
I can't find Nadeshiko anywhere.
Wait, why would she go
after telling you not to...
This isn't for sure, but she
might've gone to look for Shiny Stones.
Shiny Stones?
Because I wanted some...
I see.
That sounds like something she'd do.
Let's go find her!
Calm down. There are
Magical Monsters in that forest.
But...
And the forest itself is really big...
In that case...
I'm sorry to bring you out here so early.
Don't even worry about it!
You and I are buddies!
I wonder if Nadeshiko is all right.
I'm sure she's okay.
Nadeshiko is strong.
Stop!
This smell...
Whoa...
There aren't that many targets I can't hit.
Thanks...
If one of those things got Nadeshiko...
Nadeshiko!
I heard something from over there!
Wait!
Nadeshiko! Nadeshiko!
I'm right here!
Nadeshiko?!
Kaede...
I'll save you right now!
Just wait!
Kaede!
Nadeshiko?!
Nadeshiko!
Take my hand!
One more time!
Please...
Kaede!
Hang on!
Hurry!
That's enough.
At this rate, you'll also...
The Shikigami!
No!
I'll never let go!
Concentrate on the spell!
No!
Look, Tsubaki!
This is... magic?
I made it in time...
Thank you so much for everything.
I'm just glad you're okay.
Don't make us worry so much.
Okay...
Honestly. You're so useless without me around.
Kaede...
I'm sorry.
I just really wanted to make up with you.
Me, too.
Huh?
I wanted to make things better with you, too.
But I was just so scared...
I didn't know if it'd be
possible to incorporate
Yamato music into our rock music...
But I thought you'd think
I was a coward if I said that.
I understand how you feel.
I'm very scared, too.
You are?
Even then, I want to walk down
this path that has yet to be travelled.
Along with you and Tsubaki.
Nadeshiko...
Because that's what rock and roll means to me!
And I want to sing with you, too, Nadeshiko.
Well done, my beloved sisters.
I wuv, wuv, wuv you to pieces.
Tsubaki...
Stop...
It's dangerous here.
Don't worry. If something happens,
I'm sure that Tiara will save us again.
Wait, me?!
You guys sure are close.
I'm seeing them for the first time.
I'm so excited.
Thank you very much
for gathering to hear
Konohana wa Otome's new song tonight.
This is more of a rehearsal, but...
We have been reborn to bring you
some wabi-sabi rock!
Are we really going to do this?
Why not? Nadeshiko worked really hard on this.
Even if it's our destiny to wither someday...
We shall make this melody bloom!
We offer you this song of love!
We are three sisters from Yamato!
Konohana wa Otome!
Shall go forth!
haruka na akibare no sora takaku sakebe
遥かな秋晴れの 空高く叫べ
Shout high up in the clear autumn sky
ou, hai! ou, hai!
応、ハイ！ 応、ハイ！
Hurrah! Hurrah!
harakaratachi no koe nami to oshiyoseru
はらからたちの声 波と押し寄せる
The voices of my people, surging with the waves
ou, hai! ou, hai!
応、ハイ！ 応、ハイ！
Hurrah! Hurrah!
matsuri ga hajimareba daremo ga nakama sa
祭りが始まれば 誰もが仲間さ
When the festival starts, we're all in this together
benisasu odoriko ni sasowareru ga mama
紅さす踊り子に 誘われるがまま
Invited by the crimson donned dancers
yagura kumiage iza tanto sawageyo
やぐら組み上げ いざ たんと騒げよ
Let's build up the tower and make some noise
mae utae subete wo wasurete
舞え 歌え すべてを忘れて
Dance, sing, forget everything
ame arare ase wo hikarasete
雨あられ 汗を光らせて
Raining down, sweat glistening
koe kawase warera tsunagu enishi
声交わせ 我ら繋ぐ縁
Let us speak to each other, let us connect
yumeyume kanshashite
ゆめゆめ感謝して
Dream on and be grateful
karakurenai momiji no nishiki e
からくれない 紅葉の錦へ
Towards the red autumn coloured nishiki
kaze yo fuke konomama asa made
風よ吹け このまま朝まで
O wind, keep blowing until dawn
mae utae sono te hirogetanara
舞え 歌え その手広げたなら
Dance, sing, if you extend your hand
hitotsu ni nareruyo kami no manimani
ひとつになれるよ 神のまにまに
We can unite, in the will of the gods
odore night fever
踊れ　Ｎｉｇｈｔ　ｆｅｖｅｒ
Dance, night fever
Konohana is like totally awesome!
Kaede!
Konohana rocks!
This just might work!
Our next Orchestra is going to be a hit!
I feel a lot more confident now.
I feel like I got a lot of energy from them.
It feels like a flower bloomed within my heart.
Yes. My chest is feeling rather warm, too.
This must be the power of songs!
窓の外は 優しい月明かり そっと
mado no soto wa yasashii tsukiakari sotto
Outside the window, the gentle moonlight is shining softly
灯り消して 夢の橋を渡ろう
akari keshite yume no hashi wo watarou
Put out the lights and cross the bridge of dreams
消えそうで消えないヒカリが今
kie soude kienai hikari ga ima
The weakening yet everlasting light is now
まぶたの向こうの世界に広がった
mabuta no mukou no sekai ni hirogatta
Spreading out into the world behind my eyelids
色んな想いが溢れて
ironna omoi ga afurete
Various feelings are overflowing
キラキラ眩しく輝いてる
kirakira mabushiku kagayaiteru
sparklingly and dazzlingly shining
ずっと
zutto
Forever
It's shining stars
明日はどんな日になるかな
ashita wa donna hi ni naru kana
I wonder what kind of day tomorrow will be
心に映し出す景色は
kokoro ni utsushidasu keshiki wa
The scenery that is reflected in my heart
期待 涙 夢の 全部が重なった
kitai namida yume no zenbu ga kasanatta
Expectations, tears, and dreams, all of it bottled up in my heart
私のプラネタリウム
watashi no planetarium
My planetarium
ほら
hora
Look, in that star that is shining the brightest
一番輝いている あの星に
ichiban kagayaiteiru ano hoshi ni
願いかけて「おやすみ」
negai kakete oyasumi
A wish is enclosed: "Good night"