I can't... anymore...
Not enough Shut-in-ium!
Yeah...
Mary!
Hang in there!
Your wound's not that deep!
You can do it! I think we're almost there!
So if you just...
How can I possibly go on?
Huh?!
Champe, you can't just force support on people.
Okay.
Good news, Mary! Ratura said she'd carry you!
What gave you that idea?!
ひたすら描いてた虹の色
I kept drawing rainbow colours over and over
hitasura kaiteta niji no iro
もう七色じゃ足りないから
Seven colours are not enough
mou nanairo ja tarinai kara
毎日はすでにいつもを
Everyday leaps over the "usual" and enters a new chapter
mainichi wa sude ni itsumo wo
飛び越えて新章なのさ
tobikoete shinshou nano sa
物語は遥か彼方へ
The story is going beyond
monogatari wa haruka kanata e
心で鳴り出す鐘の音が
The bell toll in my heart
kokoro de naridasu kane no ne ga
少しずつ大きくなってゆく
is getting louder bit by bit
sukoshi zutsu ookiku natte yuku
その高鳴りを信じて
Believe in the excitement
sono takanari wo shinjite
一歩を踏み出せたなら
And take one step forward
ippo wo fumidaseta nara
想像以上のチカラに変わってるよ
It'll give me more power than I ever imagined
souzou ijouno chikara ni kawatteru yo
絶対なんてない
Can't be for sure
zettai nante nai
なにも
Nothing
nanimo
確信はできない
There's no guarantee
kakushin wa dekinai
だれも
No one
daremo
でもあきらめない
But I won't give up
demo akiramenai
だから
That's why
dakara
進んでくことが
I can still move forward
susundeku koto ga
できるよ
I can still move forward
dekiru yo
ここには魔法があるから
Because there's magic right in here
koko ni wa mahou ga aru kara
だって星より輝きだしたのに
It started to be brighter than the stars
datte hoshi yori kagayaki dashita no ni
立ち止まれるはずもないから
I can't stop now
tachidomareru hazu mo nai kara
時代はついに新しい幕開けを迎えたのさ
It entered into a new era
jidai wa tsui ni atarashii makuake wo mukaeta no sa
溢れた想いを輝石に込めて
Placing this overflowing feelings into this gem
afureta omoi wo kiseki ni komete
未来の方へ
And go beyond the future
saki no hou e
Luci, it's about time to leave.
Oh, that.
I'm skipping.
Wait, are you serious?
I don't have that much free time on my hands.
Not to mention, today's the day
I've been waiting for.
I wonder what this is.
Littering is bad. You get points
knocked off if you're caught.
You actually sound convincing.
What?!
That wasn't a compliment.
Eh?! This is a summons!
What?
What's that doing here?
A summons?
The academy assigns certain
assignments to specific groups.
Then they send a summons.
It's said they're assigned on
the director's whim and bias.
The summons can be anything from aid,
disaster prevention, nurturing, and such.
And that's assigned on that?
"Survey the forest."
This is a survey summons to
Lucifer-san and Angelica-san's group.
Apparently, there's a part of the forest where
travelers have encountered
supernatural phenomena.
Supernatural phenomena?
Some have reported hearing eerie singing voices
as well as other mysterious events
so it's saying to work together with
other groups to figure out what's going on.
Anything about Magical Monsters?
It appears that highly dangerous
Magical Monsters don't inhabit that area.
Could we possibly get points
if we survey the forest, then?
Of course!
Though there aren't
too many who'd go for points.
Being summoned is considered quite the honour.
I wonder if we're allowed to help, too...
That might prove difficult. The time everyone
was supposed to depart has passed
and I'm not quite sure where to go.
I guess that's out of the question, then.
We've reached the area we are to survey.
I guess we can set up camp here.
Water, temperature, humidity, and safety.
I see no problem here.
No arguments here!
This is so rock! Survival of
the fittest in the wilderness!
Being surrounded by my sisters
under the starry sky...
I know of something far scarier than
any supernatural phenomena going on here.
Are we here?
We're gonna set up camp here!
Good grief. Come on, Mary. We're here.
That was a harsh journey.
Seriously?
If we split up the tent,
ingredients, and cooking duties,
it'll cover all three groups.
Then let's split up.
Okay! I'll be in charge of eating!
Salsa-sama, those who do not work
shall starve and die.
Let's do a lottery.
That sounds fun!
I believe it's far more efficient
to split up in our usual groups.
I thought this might be a good opportunity
for all of us to get closer.
No way!
What a wonderful idea!
I couldn't possibly bear being
separated from my sisters!
This might be your chance
to gain even more little sisters.
Tsubaki Onee-chan.
A lottery's a great idea!
I've finally acquired the board game!
Wait, wasn't that...
Lucifer?!
Wait, why are you here?
Are you implying that
I'm not allowed to be here?
Don't you have a summons?
Oh, that.
I don't have time for that.
Is that okay?
Then do you mind if we accept it instead?
It's fine. Do as you please.
I'm rather busy.
Thanks!
Do you know what area's supposed to be surveyed?
Lucifer?
There's a map.
Then can we have it?
It wouldn't be any fun
to just give it to you for free.
I think we understand.
Basically, we just have to win the game, right?
Correct. We'll be tag-teaming this board game.
You might end up dropping out, so be ready.
It'll just be Angelica and I on our team.
Oh, fine. I guess I'm in.
If you win, I'll give you
the map for the summons.
You guys don't need
any alternates or anything?
Well, Rose's working right now...
Like we'd drop out of a board game. How lame.
I'll make sure you truly regret those words.
All right, let's start. Let the games begin!
Four.
Have your partner act like a rabbit.
Wait, am I the partner here?
Huh? What is this?!
Wait, why?
This board game is magical.
Its creator was rather eccentric.
You're lucky that didn't go on much longer.
I hear rabbits eat their own poop.
Like I'd ever do that!
Ugh, I knew I shouldn't have played.
You'll eventually see how fun this can be.
Two.
Player, name all the three-digit prime numbers.
What?!
What's wrong? Giving up already?
101, 103, 107...
...109, 111...
A mistake.
Guess you'll have to start over.
Curse you... 101, 103, 107, 109...
How terrifying
Wait, what are prime numbers again?
...113, 127...
What to do...
I'm not very good at cooking.
Leave it all to me!
And there you have it.
Go!
That's so rock!
This one seems good.
It seems thick and sturdy.
Then let's go ahead and mark them.
Now, let's have a look inside...
This isn't too bad.
It's lovely!
It looks nice in here, too.
But I appear to be weary from the rough trail...
Are you okay? Want me to do
something nice for you?
Oh, no. I couldn't possibly ask for someone
to coddle me other than my sisters.
Oh!
What in the world are you doing?
Would you like to join in, Emilia?
This is Cabaret on the go!
I'm not interested.
It's so pretty.
That looks delicious!
You think so?
Lemme see.
Yeah, it's definitely poisonous.
You'll die if you eat it.
Are you okay?!
I'm fine.
You're awesome!
Even if these mushrooms won't work...
Salsa-san!
What happened?!
Leave it to me!
Hiyah!
Wow—
Okay! I'll try that, too!
What a haul!
Mary-san!
Are you all right?
That looked like it hurt...
Oh?
Perhaps I should've made you our dinner.
What?
What is this?
Huh? Emilia?
What's wrong?
Did you want me to do
something nice... after... all?
You okay, Champe?
Thanks... I'm feeling better, I think.
Why'd you suggest a lottery?
You know how Mary is.
And that's exactly why I did it.
I was hoping this would help with her shyness.
Ah... I get it now.
Though I wasn't expecting her
board to malfunction.
Oh, Grandmother. What big ears
and sharp fangs you have.
You almost seem like a wolf...
Lynette...?
I see... You must be sick.
Then I'll have the cake and wine.
Here I go.
Five.
Your partner will lose ten years.
Lose ten years?
I wuv you, Tia!
Rosetta turned into Lolitta...
Oh, Rose.
Things are getting fun.
How?!
Oh, you look delicious, too, Grandmother...
Lynette?!
Huh? Wait, what was I doing?
Here I go!
There, there.
One.
Tag team a song and dance!
What?!
Damn it... Fine. We're singing, Angelica.
Wait, seriously?!
Can you sing?
You shouldn't push yourselves too much...
What?! Who do you think I am?
I'll let you have the honour of
hearing the best song ever.
Gimme candy, let's go!
Hello, hello!
The two of us are...
...Sadistic Candy!
I hope you all have an angelic time!
What a weird old lady.
Who're you callin' old, huh?!
Let's get singing already.
yume no naka de machiawase
夢の中で待ち合わせ
Let's rendezvous in the middle of a dream
kimi to futari de iku yo! dreaming wonderland!
君と二人で行くよ! dreaming wonderland!
I'm coming with you! dreaming wonderland!
hyappiki me no hitsuji door wo hataite
100匹目の羊 ドアをたたいて
Knocking on the door of the 100th sheep
yume no sekai e totsunyu da!
夢の世界へ突入だ！
Entering the world of the dream!
ah kirakira ticket wo te ni irete
ah キラキラチケットを 手に入れて
Ah, I've got my shiny ticket
te wo tsunaide passing gate!
手を繋いで passing gate!
Hand in hand, passing gate!
youkoso koko wa ne kizutsukanai sekai da
ようこそ ここはね「傷つかない世界」だ
Welcome to a world where nothing can hurt you
saa nani mo kamo zenbu wasurete
さあ 何もかも全部忘れて
Forget everything and everyone
pierrot to uma ni notte
ピエロと 馬に乗って
On a horse with a clown
guru guru mawarou yo! so good!
グルグル回ろうよ! so good!
We'll go round and round and round! So good!
nandemo dekichau kibun da
何でも出来ちゃう気分だ
I feel like I can do anything
hocus! pocus! saikyou juumon da
hocus! pocus! 最強呪文だ
Hocus! Pocus! The strongest spell
isseno de issho ni tobikome
いっせーので 一緒に飛び込め
Come on, jump with me!
positive★paradise
ポジティフ★パラダイス
Positive★paradise
nantoka naru jan shinpai nai jan
なんとかなるじゃん心配ないじゃん
It's gonna be all right, don't worry
hocus! pocus! zettai muteki da
hocus! pocus! 絶対無敵だ
Hocus! Pocus! I'm invincible!
welcome youkoso dreaming wonderland!
welcome ようこそ dreaming wonderland!
Welcome to dreaming wonderland!
miracle power!
ミラクルパワー!
Miracle power!
You two are amazing!
I'm shocked.
I wish I could hear more.
Thanks, everyone!
This is how it goes when I actually try.
You're really good, old lady.
Again, who the hell are you calling old?!
We sang, we ate... This is the life.
At this rate, our next Orchestra will be a hit!
You should be in our next one, too, Mary.
You already know
the choreography, don't you?
Now, you just need to practice.
But...
I'll probably just mess up
and cause you two trouble.
Hey, I mess up all the time.
No one would laugh at your hard work.
But...
I guess we can turn in for the night.
Let us know whenever you're ready.
'Kay...
Oh, I'm not a mackerel...
You okay... there?
Six.
Blank.
I'm safe... but...
Ashley!
Th-The rest is up to y—
Looks like another one dropped out.
But if I roll more than a four,
I'll make it to the goal!
True.
Here I go.
Be careful.
Go!
Two.
Your partner will do a thousand push-ups.
Push-ups?
I'm sorry!
Don't worry about it!
We've basically won our next turn!
I'll do a thousand or even 10,000!
Then do 10,000.
I was kidding! Wait, why did you respond?
One, two, three...
So close yet so far.
Yes, but if you roll anything other than
a six, I get another turn, and—
Say no more.
You never know what could happen.
Huh?
Three.
Yes!
Lucky chance! You get another roll.
No way...
Games aren't always fair, you know.
Five.
Goal! Congratulations!
Two hundred and...
We lost...
You were so close.
That was pretty fun.
If you still insist on having this map...
Huh? You'll give it to us?
One more round.
Today was a lot of fun.
Today was rockin'!
We didn't come here to play, you know.
We'll have to start surveying
the area tomorrow.
Okay! Let's do this thing!
Emilia, is something wrong?
Huh? No, I'm fine.
My lady, could it be...
Rather than holding it in,
you should go relieve yourself outside.
What are you talking about?!
Apparently, supernatural phenomena
occur around here.
Wh-What about that?
Perhaps something will happen tonight.
Wh-Wh-Wh-What are you talking about?!
Really?!
Stop being ridiculous and go to sleep.
Today was rather unfortunate.
Should we try again tomorrow?
Sorry, but I don't think I'll last.
Me, neither...
I think we might have to give up.
Yeah, you're right...
Hey, I got the map!
What?!
That's amazing!
Well done!
I'm surprised Lucifer-san let you have it.
Nah, I just got it from the director.
Of course!
Well done getting it from her!
Actually, I...
We should get ready immediately!
Let's get some sleep and leave before sunrise!
Ehh?!
I don't wanna go early in the morning.
We don't have time to complain about that.
I'll smack you awake if I have to.
Aw...
窓の外は 優しい月明かり そっと
mado no soto wa yasashii tsukiakari sotto
Outside the window, the gentle moonlight is shining softly
灯り消して 夢の橋を渡ろう
akari keshite yume no hashi wo watarou
Put out the lights and cross the bridge of dreams
消えそうで消えないヒカリが今
kie soude kienai hikari ga ima
The weakening yet everlasting light is now
まぶたの向こうの世界に広がった
mabuta no mukou no sekai ni hirogatta
Spreading out into the world behind my eyelids
色んな想いが溢れて
ironna omoi ga afurete
Various feelings are overflowing
キラキラ眩しく輝いてる
kirakira mabushiku kagayaiteru
sparklingly and dazzlingly shining
ずっと
zutto
Forever
It's shining stars
明日はどんな日になるかな
ashita wa donna hi ni naru kana
I wonder what kind of day tomorrow will be
心に映し出す景色は
kokoro ni utsushidasu keshiki wa
The scenery that is reflected in my heart
期待 涙 夢の 全部が重なった
kitai namida yume no zenbu ga kasanatta
Expectations, tears, and dreams, all of it bottled up in my heart
私のプラネタリウム
watashi no planetarium
My planetarium
ほら
hora
Look, in that star that is shining the brightest
一番輝いている あの星に
ichiban kagayaiteiru ano hoshi ni
願いかけて「おやすみ」
negai kakete oyasumi
A wish is enclosed: "Good night"