Director?
Aw, she's not here.
ひたすら描いてた虹の色
I kept drawing rainbow colours over and over
hitasura kaiteta niji no iro
もう七色じゃ足りないから
Seven colours are not enough
mou nanairo ja tarinai kara
毎日はすでにいつもを
Everyday leaps over the "usual" and enters a new chapter
mainichi wa sude ni itsumo wo
飛び越えて新章なのさ
tobikoete shinshou nano sa
物語は遥か彼方へ
The story is going beyond
monogatari wa haruka kanata e
心で鳴り出す鐘の音が
The bell toll in my heart
kokoro de naridasu kane no ne ga
少しずつ大きくなってゆく
is getting louder bit by bit
sukoshi zutsu ookiku natte yuku
その高鳴りを信じて
Believe in the excitement
sono takanari wo shinjite
一歩を踏み出せたなら
And take one step forward
ippo wo fumidaseta nara
想像以上のチカラに変わってるよ
It'll give me more power than I ever imagined
souzou ijouno chikara ni kawatteru yo
絶対なんてない
Can't be for sure
zettai nante nai
なにも
Nothing
nanimo
確信はできない
There's no guarantee
kakushin wa dekinai
だれも
No one
daremo
でもあきらめない
But I won't give up
demo akiramenai
だから
That's why
dakara
進んでくことが
I can still move forward
susundeku koto ga
できるよ
I can still move forward
dekiru yo
ここには魔法があるから
Because there's magic right in here
koko ni wa mahou ga aru kara
だって星より輝きだしたのに
It started to be brighter than the stars
datte hoshi yori kagayaki dashita no ni
立ち止まれるはずもないから
I can't stop now
tachidomareru hazu mo nai kara
時代はついに新しい幕開けを迎えたのさ
It entered into a new era
jidai wa tsui ni atarashii makuake wo mukaeta no sa
溢れた想いを輝石に込めて
Placing this overflowing feelings into this gem
afureta omoi wo kiseki ni komete
未来の方へ
And go beyond the future
saki no hou e
Are you okay, Lyn-chan?
You should breathe in through
your nose and breathe out of your mouth.
You breathed in too much!
Do we still have a ways to go?
Hmm... Just a bit further, I think.
I hate to ask... but your sense
of direction is fine, right?
Huh? I dunno.
Mary!
Where are you, Mary?!
Say something if you can hear us!
Mary?!
What's wrong?
Tiara?!
What are you doing here?
We got the summons from Lucifer and—
Have you seen Mary?!
What happened?
We haven't seen her since this morning.
We haven't seen her.
I wonder if she got lost.
You don't know where she could've gone?
Mary!
Where art thou?
We all split up and have been looking for her.
If she's hurt somewhere...
We'll help, too.
Yeah. The more the better.
It'll be nothing but rough sailing from here!
Thanks...
Rose, you take care of Lynette.
All right.
I'm sorry...
Here, I'll lead you to our tent.
Thanks.
It's rather peculiar that even
Salsa-sama can't track her scent.
Her scent just disappeared.
Did she get kidnapped
by an eagle, or something?
I'm not certain, but perhaps this has to do
with the supernatural phenomena.
Huh?!
There have rare been cases in forests
and mountains where people are taken
and people believe that it might've been
the work of spirits such as fairies or rusalki.
Such nonsense.
So, uh... What happens to those people?
According to rumours...
Their personalities completely change,
they don't remember the incident at all,
or they were just playing at someone's house.
There's no solid answer.
Playing at someone's house?
My, my...
What a lovely mountain cottage.
The doors...
They were closed yesterday.
Well, we should probably head in.
What?! We're going in?!
Could it be... that you're scared?
Sca— Of course, I'm not scared!
I don't sense anyone's presence.
I knew it. It must be—
Huh?!
Wait, what's going on?!
To think that even your brute strength
isn't enough to open them...
Who are you calling a brute?!
Well, let us proceed.
Huh? Alpha, wait!
I told you to wait!
Mary!
Hey!
If you can hear us, answer us!
My sisters are looking around here.
Then I'll search around this valley...
You can get some rest here.
I'm really sorry about this.
We need to look out for each other.
"Witches, be the light for
thy neighbour," and such.
That's...
One of Ray's best lines.
I'm a huge fan.
Me, too. I was so moved
after seeing their Orchestra.
No unit could possibly surpass Ray!
Ah, I see you're a lady of culture, as well.
Let's chat about them when we have more time.
Yes!
First, we need to find Mary!
How strange... Did this cottage
always seem this big?
This space has been warped.
What do you mean, Alpha?!
You called, I appeared, and...
Don't scare me like that!
I was trying to calm your nerves.
What in the world is this?
It's so rundown.
There's something really eerie about it.
Yeah...
This is Mary's!
Huh?! Does that mean...
She's inside?
Mary!
Champe!
I'll go with her,
so you two go tell everyone else!
Okie-dokie!
Roger.
Wait, Champe!
Mary!
Let's stay calm and look for her. Okay?
Thanks for worrying about me. I'm fine.
Rip, rip, shattering
So soft, it's almost scary
My honest feelings come pouring out of me
You're really good.
We need a little pick me up at times like this.
And our Orchestra's coming up,
so I have to practice.
Your Orchestra?
I'm in a unit called Sugar Pockets!
I hope you'll come see us!
Of course. I'll be there.
Are you in a unit with the other two?
Just Ratura. We want Mary to join,
but she's so shy...
I see... Well, I hope you get
to perform together someday.
Yeah.
Say, Ashley.
What is it, Lavie?
Where's everyone else?
I haven't the slightest.
Mary wouldn't be in a place
like this, would she?
Why are you going this far
out of your way, my lady?
Isn't it obvious?
So she's important to you?
I wouldn't say that, but we
should all help each other out.
So right now, I'm doing everything
that I can possibly do.
I see. This must be what you call chivalry.
That's not exactly it, either...
Oh? Is something the matter?
What? You can't hear that?!
That crying... That has nothing
to do with Maryberry, right?
I don't think so...
I think it's that room.
This must be it.
It stopped?
It appears so.
Honestly, what's going on?
It's not like ghosts exist.
But they do.
I mean, look behind you, my lady.
What was that...?
My heart went a pitter-patter
and a thump-thump.
This isn't the time to joke around!
Yes, but that was a ghost...
Huh? Emilia?
It's Tiara-sama.
What a coincidence, seeing you here.
What happened to Emilia?
No need to worry.
Huh? You're here, too, Alpha?
I got to see my lady's cute side,
so we should probably call it a night.
That itself is another form of chivalry.
Are you not affected because
you're an Enchanted Doll?
Affected by?
Even if you touch Emilia...
Salsa-sama and I are demihumans.
Energy Drain has no effect on us.
I see...
This is...
The entrance we came through.
We're back at the start.
Alpha?
Is there something wrong with that doll?
Hey! Wait!
It talked?!
Damn it!
We're saved...
It appears that you must be punished.
Wait, wait, wait! My bad! I'm sorry!
So please?
She did this?
Yes.
Then Mary... Do you know where Mary is?!
Mary? Who's that?
Well, let's split her legs open.
I finally caught up with you.
Excuse me... Did Marianne-san
do something rude?
Looks like the star has arrived.
She goes to our school?
I apologize for scaring you earlier.
I was just trying to greet you,
but I probably got too excited.
Champe?
Mary?!
What are you doing here?
Mary!
Oh, so Mary's that little shrimp.
Why didn't you just say so—
Silence.
Wait... Did I make you all worry?
Of course, you did!
But I'm so glad you're safe.
I'm sorry...
Maryberry-san, are these your...
Yes, we're her friends.
Ah, so these are friends...
So, what's she doing here?
Oh, well...
I met her by the river last night.
She suddenly passed out,
so I took her home with me...
Er, I decided to take her back to care for her.
We were enjoying some tea
when all of you arrived.
I was scared at first, but she took care of me.
Thank you, um...
My name is Garnet.
Thank you, Garnet-san.
Tiara, Alpha, thank you, too.
And Emilia.
Everyone's worried, so let's head back.
Okay.
Maryberry-san.
About what we talked about earlier...
I believe that you must speak your feelings,
or they won't be heard.
Marianne-san has also told me that
failure leads to success before.
So please, do your best.
I will also do my best.
Okay!
I'll do my best!
I failed to make friends yet again...
Again?
Well, I want to make some friends,
so I invite anyone I encounter to this house,
but everyone always seems to run away...
Well, that's probably because...
Because?
Never mind.
You break your back for nothing.
You appear to have been through a lot,
though you don't seem to have
any bones to break.
You are very kind.
If you're going to possess anyone,
please go to Lady Emilia instead.
She is far kinder than I. By a megaton.
So she'll be my friend?
Good morning, my lady.
Are you all right?
Who is she?!
If you touch me—
She's also a demihuman, so it'll be all right.
Oh, no wonder.
She also appears to want to be
your friend, my lady.
Well, she apparently goes to our school,
so I wouldn't mind being your friend.
Really?!
It's always favourable to find more comrades.
Thank you so much!
So cold!
I have truly witnessed your chivalry, my lady.
Oh, my.
I'm such a scatterbrain.
I forgot to serve you all tea.
I'll go make some right now.
Huh?!
Wait, what just happened?
Is something the matter?
Sh-She just... w-w-went through...
Well, she is a ghost.
But you just said she was a demihuman!
Ghosts are fine demihumans.
Is there a problem?
And you're...
I was born here.
It just talked!
Please quiet down, my lady.
I don't even know how, but one day,
I was able to see and hear.
I used to be surrounded by a bunch of humans,
but eventually, I ended up alone.
That was a long time ago,
so I don't remember it well.
One day, I happened to meet Garnet
who was wandering around.
We're kindred spirits.
I wanted to grant Garnet's wish.
So wait, could the supernatural
phenomena in the summons...
Are probably due to this doll
and Garnet-sama.
But...
It appears you went a bit too far earlier.
Well, uh... You know.
Garnet was busy dealing with
the shri— Maryberry-san earlier,
so I thought I'd have some fun with you guys.
I guess I'll let it slide this once.
Well, if that girl is a ghost...
Who exactly is she?
Garnet only remembers her name.
She doesn't even think
of herself as a ghost.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Oh, did I scare you again?
My magic that allows me to pass through
walls makes people think I'm a ghost.
I do beg your pardon, but your body
has long departed this world,
so your soul should probably follow sui—
—You stupid Junk Doll!
To suggest I've died like that. You're so funny.
But I'm extremely scared of ghosts,
so don't frighten me too much.
Um...
Don't you dare say it.
All right, everyone. Thank you all for waiting.
Garnet.
You should join our group.
Group?
You mean you're not going to spend
the rest of your lives here with me?
No. Instead, you should re-enrol in the academy.
Academy?
Yes.
You'll be able to make new memories.
And you'll be able to make a lot of friends.
That's quite lovely!
But...
You're the only friend I need, Emilia-san.
Uh, er... I suddenly feel a chill...
I'm so happy to see you so
happy, my lady.
How?!
闇夜に浮かべた Ｓａｐｐｈｉｒｅ
yamiyo ni ukabeta sapphire
A Sapphire floats in the dark night
長い睫毛を揺らす Ｄｒｅａｍｅｒ
nagai matsuge wo yurasu dreamer
Batting long eyelashes, a Dreamer
鍵をつけたままの Ｎｉｇｈｔｍａｒｅ
kagi wo tsuketa mama no nightmare
Locked in with a key, a Nightmare
聴く振素りも見せない Ｓｈｏｏｔｉｎｇ ｓｔａｒｓ
kiku soburi mo misenai Shooting stars
Can't show whether they're listening, the Shooting stars
奇々怪々
kiki kaikai
Mysterious and strange
なぜか心臓が跳ねる
naze ka shinzou ga haneru
Somehow my heart is leaping
子猫みたいに
koneko mitai ni
Just like a kitten
Ｋｎｏｃｋ されてるってわかってるけど
Knock sareteru tte wakateru kedo
I know that it was knocking
応えたらセカイが牙を剥いた
kotaetara sekai ga kiba wo muita
But when I answered, the world bared its fangs
始まりを始めから始めたくても
hajimari wo hajime kara hajimetakute mo
Even when I want to start from the beginning
踏み出せなくて
fumidasenakute
I can't step forward
Ｈｉｄｅ　ａｗａｙ
Hide away
Ｓｃａｒｙ　Ｓｔｏｒｙ　Ｎｉｇｈｔ
Scary Story Night
ユラユラと
yurayurato
Swaying
真昼のように照らしてる
mahiru no youni terashiteru
It's shining like it's midday
勇気だして
yuuki dashite
Pluck up your courage
そばにいて
sobaniite
Beside me
氷も融かせるきっと
koori motokaseru kitto
It can surely melt the ice
嘆きの　Ｋｉｓｓ
nageki no kiss
Kiss of lamentation
似合わない
niawanai
Does not suit you
髪を撫でる指先が
kami wo naderu yubisaki ga
The fingertips stroking your hair
魔法かける
mahou kakeru
Is enchanted with magic
眠らせて
nemurasete
Sleep well
我儘な夢を一緒に捜して
wagamama na yume wo issho ni sagashite
Let's search for a selfish dream together
Infinity dream
千年も先まで
sennen mo saki made
Even if it's until 1000 years ahead