ひたすら描いてた虹の色
I kept drawing rainbow colours over and over
hitasura kaiteta niji no iro
もう七色じゃ足りないから
Seven colours are not enough
mou nanairo ja tarinai kara
毎日はすでにいつもを
Everyday leaps over the "usual" and enters a new chapter
mainichi wa sude ni itsumo wo
飛び越えて新章なのさ
tobikoete shinshou nano sa
物語は遥か彼方へ
The story is going beyond
monogatari wa haruka kanata e
心で鳴り出す鐘の音が
The bell toll in my heart
kokoro de naridasu kane no ne ga
少しずつ大きくなってゆく
is getting louder bit by bit
sukoshi zutsu ookiku natte yuku
その高鳴りを信じて
Believe in the excitement
sono takanari wo shinjite
一歩を踏み出せたなら
And take one step forward
ippo wo fumidaseta nara
想像以上のチカラに変わってるよ
It'll give me more power than I ever imagined
souzou ijouno chikara ni kawatteru yo
絶対なんてない
Can't be for sure
zettai nante nai
なにも
Nothing
nanimo
確信はできない
There's no guarantee
kakushin wa dekinai
だれも
No one
daremo
でもあきらめない
But I won't give up
demo akiramenai
だから
That's why
dakara
進んでくことが
I can still move forward
susundeku koto ga
できるよ
I can still move forward
dekiru yo
ここには魔法があるから
Because there's magic right in here
koko ni wa mahou ga aru kara
だって星より輝きだしたのに
It started to be brighter than the stars
datte hoshi yori kagayaki dashita no ni
立ち止まれるはずもないから
I can't stop now
tachidomareru hazu mo nai kara
時代はついに新しい幕開けを迎えたのさ
It entered into a new era
jidai wa tsui ni atarashii makuake wo mukaeta no sa
溢れた想いを輝石に込めて
Placing this overflowing feelings into this gem
afureta omoi wo kiseki ni komete
未来の方へ
And go beyond the future
saki no hou e
Tia-chan!
Yes!
We did it!
Correct!
Heck yeah!
Too bad.
Next!
Hup!
Not bad!
I think things
might just work out.
Yeah. I'm starting
to see some hope.
At this rate, we might be
able to avoid expulsion.
It's all thanks to me, the ace!
You really are doing amazing
this term, Lavie-san.
Yay! Praise me more!
You might finally be average now.
That's not a compliment, is it?
This is all thanks to our hard work.
Do you have a moment?
Coco.
Delivery time.
I have two notifications for you.
Is your group in charge
of deliveries this week, Coco-san?
Yup. We received a summons.
Lucky...
Lily's complaining, saying, "This is too lame."
Sounds like someone I know.
Hmm?
Well, see you later.
Sure. Thank you.
Yes!
"To reward you for your assistance in
investigating the supernatural phenomena,
your group has been awarded ten points."
Yes!
We're finally seeing the light.
What's the other one?
This one's... from the director.
I can't believe we got
a notification from her personally!
Maybe we're getting a bonus
for all our hard work!
Calm down, calm down...
Let's see...
"Because you took the map
for the investigation"...
..."from the director's office
without permission
you are being deducted 70 points."
Lavie...
You Silly Rabbit!
What possessed you
to take it without permission?!
But... But... I left a note saying
we were gonna borrow it!
The director wasn't there so
what was I supposed to do?!
Honestly!
Sorry...
Forget about that.
You went to get that map for our sake.
Yes. I probably would've done the same.
Tia-chan... Rose-chan...
Well, it was because of that map that
we got to help out with that investigation.
Ashley...
Though we lost points because of it.
Well, Silly Rabbit's always
just going to be a Silly Rabbit.
What do we do now?
I mean...
Even if we received all of
the remaining points this term...
Don't worry!
Tia...
We still have some time,
so it's too early to give up!
That's true.
You said it, Tia-chan!
Let's all do our best to become
the best witches we can be!
Yeah!
At this rate, my sister's going to laugh at me.
Your sister?
My older sister was a witch.
She was just so cool and wonderful.
I want to be just like her.
Huh, I never knew that about you, Tia-chan.
She must be an amazing witch
if she's your sister, Tiara-san.
Ueh?
Uh... Yeah.
Okay, everyone.
Let's stop being depressed and eat!
Yeah!
A healthy mind starts with a healthy meal.
We can think later.
Yeah. I'm sure we can figure something out!
Or so I said, but... What should we do?
Seriously... What are you even doing?
Emilia...
I heard what's going on. Sounds rough.
Yeah...
Well, uh... If something's troubling you,
I guess I wouldn't mind hearing you out.
Huh?
I'm saying...
You want Tiara-san to feel better,
don't you, Emilia-san?
Wha— Of course not! I was just...
You're not fooling anyone.
I know everything about you, Emilia-san.
Emilia.
Thank you.
Wh-What are you thanking me for?!
I told you that's not it!
My, my. You need to be
more honest with yourself.
Mary-san agreed?
Yeah. She suddenly got motivated.
That's wonderful.
Looks like that trip to
the mountains did us some good.
Sugar Pockets may end up
being like Ray someday.
Yeah, that's aiming a bit high there.
I'm sure you can do it, Rara-chan.
You think so?
Were those two always that close?
Apparently, they hit it off.
It's rare to see Lynette talking that much.
Ratura-chan!
We need to practice one more time!
And nothing beats the bath right after!
Okay.
She's been like that for a while.
That's very promising.
Make sure you come see us, Lynette!
Yes, of course!
Okay, everyone. Let's hurry!
You're going to trip if you hurry like that.
Why do they always have Orchestras
in different locations every time?
Because they can't cover
the whole city at once.
They're maintaining a balance
by gathering mana district by district.
If they keep performing in the same spot,
everything becomes unbalanced.
Oh, that's why...
That's sort of amazing.
Even that light is being
supported by everyone's songs
and help from everyone in the city.
Yeah...
Ray was even more amazing!
Huh?
Ray is the unit that Eliza-sama was in.
Wow, you actually know what
you're talking about for once.
Heh.
Huh?
Ray was able to make their songs carry magic!
And by doing so, they were able
to amplify their magic even more.
Wow, you can do that...?
Ray's the only unit that
managed to pull that off,
though Yue and the rest
of supernova's getting close.
Yue-san and the rest of supernova...
Rara-chan!
Go on, Mary.
Um... I'm Maryberry.
I'm still new at this,
but thank you for having me!
And now...
...Sugar Pockets is gonna...
...steal all of your hearts!
ココロはキャラメリゼ
kokoro wa caramelized
Your heart is caramelized
only you
Only you
sweet and bitter heart
Sweet and bitter heart
フキゲンに むくれた顔の lovely baby
fukigen ni mukureta kao no lovely baby
In a bad mood, the pouting face of a lovely baby
paya, paya
Paya, paya
おはようの ハグもかわされて lonely
ohayou no hagu mo kawasarete lonely
In the mornings, avoiding the hugs-so lonely
paya, paya
Paya, paya
どしたの そっぽ向いたままで you said
doshitano soppo mui tama made you said
What's wrong? You kept facing the other way, you said
ナニカナ
nanikana
What is it?
あなたのせいで モヤモヤするの
anata no sei de moyamoya suruno
It's your fault, so I won't tell you
理由は教えない!
riyuu wa oshienai!
why I'm feeling depressed!
困らされちゃうのも 悪くないよ
komara sarechau no mo warukunai yo
It's not that bad to be in a fix
Huh?
Did that tower change colours?
飾らない君を 知りたいんだ
kazaranai kimi wo shiritainda
I want to get to know the unadorned you
That's the Metrics Tower.
It changes colour depending on
how much mana it fills up with.
いつか見つけたカフェに行こうよ
itsuka mitsuketa kafe ni ikou yo
Let's go to the cafe that we found that time
Huh...
そんなに拗ねないで
sonna ni sunenai de
so don't keep holding yourself back
甘く焦がれたココロつつけば
amaku kogareta kokoro tsutsukeba
If you poke at your sweetly-in-love heart
パリパリとひび割れて
paripari to hibiwarete
It will crisply crumble
怖いくらい柔らかい
kowai kurai yawarakai
It's scarily soft and squishy
素直な想いがあふれだす
sunao na omoi ga afuredasu
and honest feelings are overflowing
君がくれる言葉や仕草
kimi ga kureru kotoba yashigusa
All the words and gestures that you express to me
They're so sparkly.
すべてが大好きだから
subete ga daisuki dakara
I love them all
Yes.
Couldn't we do that, too?
できるだけ受け止めたいんだ
dekirudake uketometainda
I want to take it in as much as I can
Huh?
Tia-chan?
You can get points
doing an Orchestra, right?
いつもそばにいて
itsumo soba ni ite
being always by your side
Yes, but...
わがままキャラメリゼ
wagamama caramelized
I'm selfishly caramelized
You're such a kidder. I mean...
only you
Only you
sweet and bitter heart
Sweet and bitter heart
Can you actually picture us
standing up there?
Nope, not happening. No way, José.
I guess you're right.
I did some calculations.
The most you can get from completely filling
the tower with mana is 80 points.
If we can get it to 72%, we get 57 points.
If we add the points from our remaining classes,
we'll just barely escape failing.
What are you talking about?
They're wondering if we
should put on an Orchestra...
Uehhh?!
Not to mention, 72%?
I'm pretty sure the tower turns yellow at 70%.
And yellow means...
We'll have to surpass Sugar Pockets'
performance yesterday.
Even an ace has things that she can't pull off.
Yeah, I don't think we can...
Do you all want to be expelled?
Well...
I know it seems impossible.
But I want to take the chance
if there's even the slightest possibility.
I don't want to just sit here
and do nothing. Not to mention...
I sort of want to sing now, too.
Not just Sugar Pockets, but IV KLORE,
and Konohana wa Otome...
And supernova...
They're all shining
when they're doing their Orchestra.
They inspired me.
It's not just about the points. I want to sing.
I really want to sing!
Same here!
I guess... it wouldn't hurt to try,
even knowing we might fail.
Tia.
Let's do our best.
Um, please wait a moment.
There's no way we could
possibly do an Orchestra!
Have no fear! We'll just go out with a bang!
Huh?
My father always said,
"Think of adversity as an opportunity."
Lynette.
You don't have to answer us immediately,
but could you at least think about it?
I see. Sure, why not?
I have no reason to stop you.
Yeah, we're going to do everything we can.
Thanks for cheering me up the other day.
Er, I... That's not why I said that...
Emilia?
It's just you never know when
and where she'll pop up from...
We'll do our best to keep up with IV KLORE!
Well, that's rather bold of you.
I hope you'll come see our Orchestra
if you have a chance.
Well, I guess I might go
see it if I feel like it.
Do your best.
Yeah, we will.
What's the meaning of this?
Yue-san...
You're going to put on an Orchestra?
Yes, we're thinking of—
You can't be serious.
You really think just because
you're Eliza-sama's little sister...
What?!
So you did know.
I had no idea.
So you're Eliza-sama's little sister?
You should model for me
so I can draw you sometime!
Huh? Model?!
Don't worry. It's only scary at first!
But I...
You can totally do it!
Regardless.
I'll never acknowledge you.
Why? We just want to sing like you—
Don't compare me with you.
The reason I sing is so that
our songs can carry our magic
and to protect the people.
And...
We're going to exterminate
every last Magical Monster.
I have much more on the line than you do.
Sorry about that.
Yue-chin's always so serious.
Yue's the princess of LongDu.
Yes, I heard about that.
Oh? Well, aren't you in the know?
A few years back, LongDu was
attacked by Magical Monsters.
Apparently, there were a lot of casualties.
But that's when...
...Eliza-sama and the rest of Ray showed up!
Eliza, Chloe, Angers, Camilla, Yuzuriha...
As Ray, they used their magic and song
to exterminate the Magical Monsters,
and LongDu was saved.
They're basically saviors!
Wait, Chloe...?
Yeah, she's our director.
What?!
Oh, you didn't know?
Director Chloe was a member of Ray?
After peace was restored, Eliza-sama
stayed in LongDu a little while longer.
And the one who she mentored was Yue.
So Yue-san was...
Basically, they're master and pupil.
Fiona-san, Millefeuille-san... Thank you!
I'll try talking to Yue-san more!
Good luck!
She really is a kind person.
Right!
Eliza-sama!
Yue...
Is it true that you're
going back to Waleland?
Yes, it is.
No...
Thank you for everything.
No... I should be thanking you.
But... I wanted to learn more!
Thank you. But I have to go home.
I'm sure that my little sister
has been longing to see me.
Little sister?
Yue.
If you truly want to become a witch,
then you should knock on the doors
of Flora Girls Academy in Malmcester.
Do you think I can be
an amazing witch like you, Eliza-sama?
That's all up to you.
But just maybe...
Yue-san!
I heard about you and my sister.
They never know when to shut up.
I think we're sort of alike, Yue-san.
How?
You and I both want to be
an amazing witch like my sister.
Whenever I was sick,
my sister would sing to make me feel better.
All of your Orchestras did the same.
That's why I also want to be
a witch to bring people happiness.
Those are the kinds of songs I want to sing.
I know this because I saw supernova perform.
I know that you love to sing!
But when you told me
why you were singing earlier,
you seemed to be in so much pain...
Well...
Aren't songs essentially people's feelings?
I felt all your feelings you put into your song.
My feelings?
That's why next time,
I want you to feel my feelings at our Orchestra.
Though I don't know if it'll go as planned...
I seriously can't with you.
Do as you please.
Huh?
If you miserably get expelled,
I'd feel bad for Eliza-sama.
Lynette?
Hello?
Rara-chan...
Wassup?
I could ask the same. This is a rare sight.
I'm just looking something up.
A book on fashion?
Yeah. Making costumes is super hard.
But I want to help those two out
as much as I can.
Help them...
I see.
I was hoping that I could at least
help with some lyrics, but...
Why did you start doing Orchestras, Rara-chan?
I always loved watching them,
and one day, I wanted to do one, too.
That's all it is, really.
You like Ray, too, so I'm sure
you're interested in singing.
Well, yes...
The fact that you're unsure about this means
that there's a part of you
that wants to do this, right?
"Suffering and conflict
are both darkness and light.
Do not fear the path you've chosen. Embrace it!"
Isn't that Chloe-sensei's...
Her famous quote from her days in Ray...
Tiara-san!
What's the matter, Lynette?
I'll give the Orchestra a try!
Really?! Thank you! I'm so happy!
I'm not very confident, though...
I'm not confident at all, either.
That's why we should just do everything we can.
Yes!
All right, then next...
I believe we also need the director's
permission to conduct an Orchestra.
Permission?
Yes, because this also involves
the city's districts, so...
Okay, then I'll go ask
for permission right now!
Thank you!
Come in.
Pardon me.
How may I help you?
窓の外は 優しい月明かり そっと
mado no soto wa yasashii tsukiakari sotto
Outside the window, the gentle moonlight is shining softly
灯り消して 夢の橋を渡ろう
akari keshite yume no hashi wo watarou
Put out the lights and cross the bridge of dreams
消えそうで消えないヒカリが今
kie soude kienai hikari ga ima
The weakening yet everlasting light is now
まぶたの向こうの世界に広がった
mabuta no mukou no sekai ni hirogatta
Spreading out into the world behind my eyelids
色んな想いが溢れて
ironna omoi ga afurete
Various feelings are overflowing
キラキラ眩しく輝いてる
kirakira mabushiku kagayaiteru
sparklingly and dazzlingly shining
ずっと
zutto
Forever
It's shining stars
明日はどんな日になるかな
ashita wa donna hi ni naru kana
I wonder what kind of day tomorrow will be
心に映し出す景色は
kokoro ni utsushidasu keshiki wa
The scenery that is reflected in my heart
期待 涙 夢の 全部が重なった
kitai namida yume no zenbu ga kasanatta
Expectations, tears, and dreams, all of it bottled up in my heart
私のプラネタリウム
watashi no planetarium
My planetarium
ほら
hora
Look, in that star that is shining the brightest
一番輝いている あの星に
ichiban kagayaiteiru ano hoshi ni
願いかけて「おやすみ」
negai kakete oyasumi
A wish is enclosed: "Good night"