I see.
I understand what you're trying to say.
So, please!
Let us do an Orchestra.
I guess you really are sisters.
Huh?
Everything about you reminds me of Eliza.
Director, do you...
Who do you think I am?
I'm sorry... I actually don't know
much about Ray.
Eliza didn't mention anything?
Nothing in detail. She did show me
some magic and sing me songs.
That sounds like Eliza.
But...
Whenever she did, she was really lovely!
I see.
What kind of unit was Ray?
I guess I can tell you a little story...
...about the past.
Eliza! Eliza!
Hey, let's go get some tea!
Our souls need to be
quenched with sweet liquid.
Knowing when to take a break
is important. Right, Eliza?
I guess you're right.
With Eliza at our centre, we had
Camilla,
Angers,
Yuzuriha,
and myself.
The five of us formed the unit, Ray.
Tea time is always so relaxing.
I swear, you're an old hag, Yuzuriha.
Who are you calling an old hag?!
Well, you are the oldest.
I'm the same age as you!
And you definitely look much older than me.
And I look and feel angelically
younger than you two.
Everyone knows that I'm totes
the cutest little angel in Ray.
Putting "totes" aside... Our Orchestra
the other day was quite the success.
Well, what did you expect?
Camilla, carelessness is our greatest foe!
Darkness encroaches...
upon this material world!
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Hey, everyone.
I created some new magic, so I was
wondering if I could try it out next time.
You and your research.
Ooh, what's it like?
Just watch.
There!
Wow, impressive.
This looks great.
That's so angelically pretty!
The calmness of the dawn's light has bloomed.
Wow, that's amazing!
I thought my little sister would love this.
And there it is.
You with your little sister.
You always talk about her.
Nothing is more beautiful than a song of love.
She's shown me that magic before!
She would make flowers of light dance.
It was so pretty!
I'm glad to hear it.
This picture is of Ray
when we used that magic
with the falling flowers in an Orchestra.
This is Ray...?
Director...
You seem a bit different.
We don't need to discuss me right now.
Everyone was rather bizarre...
er, rather unique in our unit.
Camilla-sama!
Camilla is a vampire.
A type of demihuman.
You're so amazing!
Hit me, too!
Silence, peasants!
You're getting in the way of my game!
Because she never gets tired or even sweats,
she was called the Immaculate Prince.
Honestly, she was just a narcissist.
With her keen insight and concentration,
Yuzuriha was always an elegant dancer.
People called her
the Graceful Dancing Princess.
Here you go.
Ah, thank you.
I offer you my greatest gratitude.
Hey!
Yuzuriha-san, did you—
What's the matter?
We're just getting to know
each other a little better.
Well? How about we head to the Cabaret?
Okay...
She had, uh, very particular interests...
Can I pwease have one again?
You're always so cute, Angers-chan.
Angers was considered a child prodigy
and had almost as much potential as Eliza.
Hello, hello!
Oh, it's you, Angers-chan.
What's wrong?
Well, I was trying to carry some
things when my knee...
Then leave it to me!
Hup.
Angel, angel, lu, lu, lu, lu, lu!
How's that?
I feel much better! Thank you.
That's angelically great!
Could you help me out, too?
Huh?
My wife got a bit angry.
I drank way too much last night.
My stomach hurts.
My head hurts so bad...
And I—
No rush, no rush!
Everyone'll get their turn!
She was so sweet and innocent.
Everyone loved her.
Her nickname was the Little Archangel.
Angel... That's really nice.
And...
Ow...
Angelica?! What are you doing?
She's Angers.
Angelica is actually
the Little Archangel Angers.
Wait... what?
What?!
Tch.
What are you looking at?
Oh, nothing...
It's because she's having a hard time
connecting you with Angers.
What?! You're the one
who spilled the beans!
That's what you get for eavesdropping.
Whaddya say?!
Oh? Do you have a problem
with me, the director?
So she really is Ray's...
Tch. Don't tell anyone. The only other one
that knows about this is Luci.
Promise the great Archangel Angers.
Okay...
You just laughed, didn't you?
No.
You're lying! You totally laughed!
You totally did.
No.
Then let me see your face!
No way.
Excuse me...
But why...
Just because. There's no huge reason.
I guess I was just tired.
I even took some time off from school,
but then she had the nerve to drag me back.
It would've been a shame to let
your talent go to waste like that.
Though I must say even I was surprised
at how much you changed.
Sh-Shut up. I'm just going through a phase.
After Eliza retired from Ray, we disbanded.
We're the only two left at this school.
The Immaculate Prince Camilla
is in Dortgart doing research on magic.
The Graceful Dancing Princess Yuzuriha
is messing around in various countries...
Er, learning about other
countries and their cultures.
Did my sister have a nickname?
Of course. Eliza's nickname
was the Scarlet Songstress.
The Scarlet Songstress...
That's perfect for my sister.
And then we have Chloe,
the Azure Reaper from Hell!
Wha—
Reaper...?
And she's the one who made
that nickname and spread it around!
How embarrassing!
That was just my youth talking...
Angelica...
That's what you get!
Miss Azure Reaper from Hell!
Would you like to offer
your life back to God?
Oh? Go ahead and try!
Oh, I'm sorry. It was just
so nice watching you two.
Well... Things were pretty crazy.
I have nothing but good memories.
And how are you doing?
I'm having a lot of fun every day.
Rosetta-san and the rest of your group...
They reminded me of us before we had Eliza.
I thought that maybe if you had joined them,
they could finally be disciplined and grow.
I see.
And...
No, I do apologize
for not giving you a choice.
It's fine. I'm actually
really grateful, Director.
I'm really happy being able to spend time
with such wonderful friends.
And you wanted to perform an Orchestra
with those friends of yours, correct?
Yes!
Well, aren't you rarin' to go?
If you're unable to reach
the minimum amount of points needed,
you are going to be expelled.
At this rate, we're going
to be expelled anyway.
And...
I really want to put on an Orchestra!
Very well.
Then...
All right. I will allow you
to put on an Orchestra.
Thank you so much!
Please show me just how much
all of you have grown.
She's been gone a while...
I wonder if something happened.
Is it that hard to get permission?
Maybe she had to undergo some trial...
Trial?
You know... She may have to do this or that!
This or that?
Everyone!
Heck yeah!
Are you okay?
Yesh...
I'm fine... This is easy...
Writing lyrics and making
costumes are both important,
but don't push yourselves too hard.
Yeah. You guys need to
actually sleep and feel refreshed.
Yeah, you know. A well-slept child
is a well-kept child.
You're amazing, Rosetta-san...
You have school and your job, too...
That's not a big deal.
You're amazing, Rose-chan.
I guess it's not surprising
your grades are as great as mine.
So is there anything else
we should be preparing?
Don't ask me.
Well...
We need to fill the sound equipment
and the lighting equipment with magic.
That's right!
For that, we need someone with knowledge
and technique to use Magical Mechanics...
But it's rather difficult...
and we don't have much time.
Oh, no...
Want some help?
I mean... only if you need it...
Maryberry.
Do you know a lot about Magical Mechanics?
Yup. I'm really good with that stuff.
Leave it to me.
Easy peasy!
Thank you so much!
That's such a big help!
No, I should be thanking you.
You all helped me out the other day...
Mary!
Maybe they'll help, too.
These should all help.
This might be a bit much.
Wow, you have a lot going on.
Kaede-san.
What in the world are you doing?
I guess I don't need to do anything.
You seem a bit jealous.
Luci! How long have you been there?!
Probably since a certain someone
looked like she wanted to join in.
That's not it at all!
So how are they doing?
Who knows? It seems they've
got stuff figured out.
Well, that's good.
It's always rough in the beginning.
All right, class.
Today is the last day of this term,
but always remember that
you're witches and act responsibly.
Always be the shining light
for those around you.
Flora-sama is always watching over
the stars, the earth, and everything else.
It's finally time.
Yeah... We did everything we could.
I'm so done with studying!
All we have left is the Orchestra.
No, not yet.
Why don't we decide a name for our unit?
Oh, a name...
Is that really necessary?
It's not absolutely necessary,
but if we had one...
I think I'd be even more hyped up
if we had a cool name.
That's true.
Then let's pick one.
Yeah!
Or so we said...
Names are hard.
Um... How about "Charming Five"?
It has a nice ring to it, don't you think?
Yeah, that's just not it.
What about Hustle Five?
Super Ultra Five, maybe?
Pretty Five GOGO?
Hold on, everyone!
First, let's drop the "Five."
You sure?
What to do...
I know! How about
Lavie-chan and her Merry Little Fri—
Get serious.
Well, you guys are taking too long.
That's not an excuse for you to fool around.
The sun's going down soon...
What should we do?
I just remembered...
Yes.
Wait, what?
The day I came to the academy,
I looked down on the town from here.
The light from the Shiny Stones was so pretty.
But now, it looks even more brilliant.
Maybe it's because I'm with all of you.
I always wanted to be the light...
...to shine down on the town, the people...
That's it, Tiara-san!
Our unit name!
It's finally time.
It's Lynette and her friends' time to shine!
It's so exciting.
Yeah!
But they're going to be expelled
if they fail, right?
If they can't fill the tower more
than 72%, to be precise.
Which means...
If they can get the Metrics Tower
to turn yellow, they should be okay.
What do you think will happen, Emilia-san?
I'm not sure.
Eliza-sama's little sister
is doing an Orchestra...
How exciting.
Right, Yue?
Hey, is it starting yet?
Yeah, they are a bit late.
When's this thing starting?
I wonder if something happened.
This is the district for today, right?
It should be...
Making us wait is a part of rock and roll, too.
Behind us!
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone!
We're performing our first Orchestra tonight!
But...
Let's not sweat the small things.
Let's all have fun...
...to our hearts' content!
We'll be the light that
shines down on everyone!
We are...
...LiGHTs!
seven hundred sextillion no sora de
In a sky of 700 sextillion
700,000,000,000,000,000,000,000 の空で
kinou made no yume wo koe ni shite
The dream that lasted till yesterday, voice it all out
昨日までの夢を声にして
What?
Wait, why are they splitting up?
Wait, are they going to do this while moving?
An Orchestra?
We should go, too!
mune ni wakidashita yuuki ga
Even if the courage that springs out from your chest
胸に湧き出した勇気が
osanakute chipoke de kowakute mo
Is small and easily scared
幼くてちっぽけで怖くても
furuete iru dake nara
If it's just the tremble
震えているだけなら
sugu kiete itte shimau kara
Then it will be gone soon
すぐ消えていってしまうから
aruite ikeru hazu no michi de
On the path that you should be able to walk on
歩いていけるはずの道で
fuan no kakera
Even if anxiety's remnants
不安のカケラ
ni tsumazuite mo
trip you up
につまずいても
hirotte dakishimete saa susumou
Pick them up, hold them tight, Let's move forward
拾って抱きしめて さあ進もう
3 2 1 Jump!
3 2 1 jump!
seven hundred sextillion no sora de
In a sky of 700 sextillion
700,000,000,000,000,000,000,000 の空で
soko ga start tte kidzuitara
If you realize that the start is there
そこがスタートって気付いたら
hashiridashitai shunkan wo
That moment when you want to start running,
走り出したい瞬間を
saa (saa) tsukamaete
Now (now) grab hold of it
さあ (さあ) 捕まえて
rokusen-nichi-me no itsumo no sora
It's the usual sky on the 6,000th day
六千日目のいつもの空
dakedo kyou kakikaetara
But if you were to redraw it today
だけど今日描きかえたら
kitto itsuka (sono ippo ga)
Then someday (That first step)
きっといつか (その一歩が)
kimi no sora ni kakaru
Will become a rainbow over your sky
君の空にかかる
niji ni naru
虹になる
We just fly to you
we just fly to you
And just sing for you
and just sing for you
Nice! Great job!
They're so energetic!
That was amazing. Wasn't it, Yue?
Well... I guess I can
acknowledge her a little bit.
Oh, Yue...
Be honest with yourself.
That felt great!
I let it all out!
Wait, the tower!
It's yellow... right?
Yeah.
That means...
That we...
We did it!
Oh-ho...
Not half bad.
Cheers!
It feels like a dream...
...that we actually did an Orchestra.
My heart is still pounding.
I wanted to sing even more!
Jeez, you're so greedy!
Like you can talk.
Was I that obvious?
We all feel the same.
We're not being expelled now,
so let's do that again.
Yeah, we should.
By the way, who used that last bit of magic?
That was Tiara-san, wasn't it?
Huh? Me?
Oh, there you are.
Now I don't have to go to your rooms.
What's the matter?
I have a message for you guys.
At this hour?
Express mail.
Thanks.
Well, see ya.
Thanks again.
Great work!
I wonder what it is.
Maybe we're being promoted
to Rouge because we did so well!
It can't be that easy.
What?!
Today's Orchestra...
Figures from districts that weren't
supposed to be measured were included...