Today's Orchestra...
Figures from districts that weren't
supposed to be measured were included...
Wait... Is it because we
flew around as we danced?
How are we supposed to know
where the district ends?
The measurement of mana
from the target district...
...was 67%...
We're going to be expelled.
ひたすら描いてた虹の色
I kept drawing rainbow colours over and over
hitasura kaiteta niji no iro
もう七色じゃ足りないから
Seven colours are not enough
mou nanairo ja tarinai kara
毎日はすでにいつもを
Everyday leaps over the "usual" and enters a new chapter
mainichi wa sude ni itsumo wo
飛び越えて新章なのさ
tobikoete shinshou nano sa
物語は遥か彼方へ
The story is going beyond
monogatari wa haruka kanata e
心で鳴り出す鐘の音が
The bell toll in my heart
kokoro de naridasu kane no ne ga
少しずつ大きくなってゆく
is getting louder bit by bit
sukoshi zutsu ookiku natte yuku
その高鳴りを信じて
Believe in the excitement
sono takanari wo shinjite
一歩を踏み出せたなら
And take one step forward
ippo wo fumidaseta nara
想像以上のチカラに変わってるよ
It'll give me more power than I ever imagined
souzou ijouno chikara ni kawatteru yo
絶対なんてない
Can't be for sure
zettai nante nai
なにも
Nothing
nanimo
確信はできない
There's no guarantee
kakushin wa dekinai
だれも
No one
daremo
でもあきらめない
But I won't give up
demo akiramenai
だから
That's why
dakara
進んでくことが
I can still move forward
susundeku koto ga
できるよ
I can still move forward
dekiru yo
ここには魔法があるから
Because there's magic right in here
koko ni wa mahou ga aru kara
だって星より輝きだしたのに
It started to be brighter than the stars
datte hoshi yori kagayaki dashita no ni
立ち止まれるはずもないから
I can't stop now
tachidomareru hazu mo nai kara
時代はついに新しい幕開けを迎えたのさ
It entered into a new era
jidai wa tsui ni atarashii makuake wo mukaeta no sa
溢れた想いを輝石に込めて
Placing this overflowing feelings into this gem
afureta omoi wo kiseki ni komete
未来の方へ
And go beyond the future
saki no hou e
Damn it!
We were so close...
Couldn't they spare a few points?
Man... The director's so narrow-minded.
What you meant to say is...
What?
She actually got it right.
I can't believe Lavie actually
sounded intelligent for once...
What?!
Maybe the shock of being expelled
was bigger than we imagined.
Are you feeling all right, Lavie-san?
Ugh! You guys are so mean!
Help me out here, Tia—
Tia...
Huh? Oh, sorry. What was that?
Hey, it's the ladies from the other day.
We really enjoyed
your performance the other day.
When's LiGHTs going to sing again?
Um...
Well...
I'm really sorry. We don't know yet.
Really?
But it'll be sometime soon,
so wait for us, okay?
Okay! I'll look forward to it!
Isn't that great?
Well, goodbye.
See you later!
Yup. See you later.
Tiara...
But LiGHTs is...
I...
I still want to sing.
I understand how you feel, but...
I still...
I still want to be a witch.
That's a really nice carriage.
No way... Why...?
Tia, is that...
We've come for you, Tiara-sama.
Wait, this is your carriage, Tiara?
Wow, you really are a noble.
Tiara-sama is not a noble.
Tia's name is...
Tiara Victoria Lex Waleland.
But isn't that...
She is the daughter of Queen Louise.
The Second Princess of Waleland.
Ehh?!
But Tiara... I mean, Tiara-sama...
I'm sorry I kept it a secret.
Tiara-sama, we must hurry.
But I'm still—
We've been informed that you have been
expelled from Flora Girls Academy.
How did you...
Please wait! Tiara-sama wants to—
Know your place!
If you're going to stand in our way...
Stop!
I'm so sorry, everyone.
Tia...
I can't believe we had
to say goodbye like this...
I just can't accept this!
Wait, Nadeshiko!
Why do Tiara-san and the others
have to be expelled?!
I understand, but...
Those are the academy rules...
I'm going to go object right now!
Onee-chan!
Calm down.
No, I'm going to charge in
the rock and roll way!
I feel the same way you do, but...
I don't think they'll undo
the expulsion even if you go...
Honestly, how unsightly.
But I sorta miss them, too.
I agree with Salsa-sama.
My lady.
Did you want to drink milk that badly?
No, I just...
This is just how I'm feeling right now!
Drinking straight from the creamer...
I must say, you're a trendsetter.
She is? You're amazing, Emilia!
Did you hear, Yue-chin?!
I heard they were expelled.
What a shame! Their Orchestra was lit, too.
Whatever.
It doesn't concern us.
But it really was amazing though.
Hey, it's raining.
We better get inside.
So Tia-chan's a princess...
Don't be rude.
Yes. We need to call her Tiara-sama.
Oh, right.
You knew, right, Rosetta-san?
Yes... But she didn't want any of you
to act unnatural around her.
I see.
But still...
Tia wanted to be our friend
and wanted to belong.
So let's not change anything.
Yeah, you're right.
Tia-chan's always going to be Tia-chan to us!
All right. I won't worry about her title, then.
Tiara's one of us.
Wait...
If Tiara-san is the Second
Princess of Waleland...
Yes. She's Eliza-sama's younger sister.
I guess you really do love Ray...
Ow.
'Sup?
No, it's nothing.
Anyway, the question is
what are we going to do now?
Oh, right.
First, we need to find a place
to stay for the night.
Would it be possible to ask one of
the places you work, Rosetta-san?
That might be difficult. I don't think
they have room for all four of us.
Whatevs. It is what it is.
I guess that means Lavie's
sleeping outdoors tonight.
Wait, why?! Let's go stay at an inn!
We need to save some money since we
don't know what the future holds for us.
Here you go.
Rara-chan.
But we didn't order this.
It's my treat. LiGHTs' Orchestra
was totally awesome!
Yay.
Thank you.
Don't mind if I do.
It looks delicious.
I'm glad you guys seem okay, though.
Both Champe and Mary
were pretty worried, too.
We can't stay depressed forever.
That's the spirit!
So where's Tiara?
I haven't seen her around.
Well...
We'll tell you later.
Yes... We can't really say here.
Oh, hey, Ratura. Do you know
a place we can spend the night?
Somewhere to spend the night?
Why not right here?
Here?
There's some space upstairs.
Want me to ask for you?
Are you sure?
Sure, fanks!
Okay, one sec.
If they'll let us stay here— Ow...
We'll be set for a while.
Yes.
Hey! You ready for the Cester Festival yet?
We're getting there.
They're supposed to go all out this year,
so we've got our work cut out for us.
Well, we've been waiting for this festival.
Hopefully the weather doesn't
turn out like today though.
Oh, right. The Cester Festival is coming up.
We just got to eat and have fun
last year. It was great.
A festival, huh...
I'm not excited at all for some reason.
Yes...
Sorry to keep you guys waiting.
They said okay!
Thank you very much.
Yes!
Now we won't have to sleep outside.
There is a condition!
You guys have to help out at the shop.
Thank you for waiting.
Here's your Nilgiri tea with lemon.
Are you ready to order?
May I get the Juicy Steak medium rare?
I'd like the broccoli salad.
Oh, and some iced coffee.
Would you like your coffee hot or cold?
Ow...
Ashley-san?
No, it's nothing.
That was a close one.
Sorry about that. Thanks.
Not a problem.
Order coming in!
I need a janky steak at minimum
rare and a bukkololi salad!
Oh, and a hot iced coffee.
Working is so hard...
It's not so bad once you get used to it.
It can actually be pretty fun.
You're amazing, Rosetta.
I had a lot of fun, too.
Yeah, and the owner said to
never let you take orders again.
Why?!
You kept messing up.
Well, you broke a plate, Ashley!
B-But that was your fault!
Don't lift the blame on me!
You mean "shift the blame"!
Can I say something?
What?!
About what we're going to do now...
Yes, we do need to think about that.
Can't we just keep doing this?
We don't actually live here, remember?
We can't just stay here forever...
About that...
I'm thinking about going home for a bit.
Ueh?!
I need to report back home since
I can't stay at the academy anymore.
I see.
You're leaving, too, Rose-chan?
It's going to get really lonely.
Well, I'm not leaving right away.
I plan to stay in Malmcester
for three or four more days.
Then let's have a going away party!
Yeah, we should! Let's have a feast!
We can't go all out though.
Boo. Ashley, you party pooper.
I don't see why not.
Let's do this!
Not you, too, Lynette.
Well, I'm sure you're all tired.
Let's get some sleep.
Lyn-chan, You can use the bed.
Wait, are you sure?
You seem the most exhausted.
What happened there?
That's Leskarka. They were attacked by
a horde of Magical Monsters the other day.
A horde of Magical Monsters?
Yes. We are looking after
some of the evacuees in Bristol.
That looks like it hurts.
Are you okay?
Look at your cute, little, rosy cheek!
Shut up, Silly Rabbit! Ow...
What can we do to help?
I'm sure it'll get better if you
rub some red peppers on there.
Are you trying to kill me?
If only one of us could use Healing Magic...
Maybe Angelica-san can heal it.
Angelica?
She healed Coco-san
at our bump ball tournament.
Oh, you're right.
Now we're all set.
Hmph. You weakling.
I know, right?
Yeah, this isn't gonna work.
Magic doesn't work on wisdom teeth.
Fwat?!
Then what should we do?
Time to go to the teeth yankers.
Teeth yankers?
Hiyah!
This is the end.
Just kill me now.
Well, I mean, at least they got the tooth out.
Yes. I'm amazed you survived that.
Just get some rest for a while.
What are you guys even doing?
What do you mean?
We're working at the café
and spending the nights the—
You're satisfied with that?
Well, what are we supposed to do?
Tiara-san's not here, either.
Hmph. Don't bother, Angelica.
No point in talking to these laggards.
What...?
Ashley...
Don't push yourself.
I don't have time to be
depressed over a tooth or two.
What? You've got a problem?
We gave it all we had.
We regret nothing.
Yeah! We did our best!
True, your Orchestra wasn't half bad.
But you're willing to let this be game over
just because you got expelled?
What's important right now
is what you guys want to do.
It's fine to be content and all,
but eventually, you're just going to get lazy.
Angelica-san...
Let's go, Angelica.
Well, do your best not to die at least.
I'll be going now.
It's going to get even lonelier now.
You still have time until the night carriage...
Well, I need to tell all
the places I worked at thanks.
You don't have to go today.
We haven't even had the going away party yet...
After Angelica and Lucifer talked to us,
I decided to think about everything myself.
I decided I needed to go now.
Why?
I'm worried about Tia.
In that case—
I'm worried about her, too!
But where I'm going isn't that close.
That's true, but...
My home is nearby, so leave it to me.
All right.
Please look after Tiara-san for us.
Lynette...
Let's see each other again soon.
You said you'd stay with me forever...
Sir, we're closed for the night.
You said forever!
Did you just need an excuse
to leave your village?!
Thank you very much.
Let's get this over with.
Yes.
Oh, there you are.
I guess it was true that
you guys were working here.
Well, they're letting us stay here, so...
What brings you all here?
We were worried about you
since we heard you were expelled.
I'm glad you're doing okay.
Ashley, what happened to your face?
Don't ask.
Where're Rosetta-san and Tiara-san?
They're...
What are you doing?
Just go chat upstairs.
But...
I'll take care of that.
Thank you very much.
I had no idea all that happened.
But wow. Tiara's a princess?
Talk about a shocker.
Lily, that's rude.
Whoops.
No, it's fine.
Tiara-san wanted us to treat her
like a friend, not a princess.
That sounds like Tiara-san.
I guess that means we won't be able
to see you perform an Orchestra again...
Wait, you saw it?
It was awesome!
It was very lovely.
We've been in a slump lately.
But seeing your Orchestra
really motivated us.
We decided to give it another shot.
—Thank you.
—Thank you very much.
Aw, you're making me blush.
We're happy to hear that.
I'm sure Tiara would be happy to hear that.
So what are you guys going to do now?
We were actually just thinking about that.
I'm not sure why you sound
so proud about that.
Our dreams of becoming witches are now...
Dreams aren't everything.
At least, that's what I thought.
I was sort of forced to go to this school, too.
But after we met Melissa and started
spending our days as a group,
our bond became my treasure.
My dream now is to protect this bond.
Coco...
So I'm sure you'll all have
new encounters and dreams.
But...
The days the five of us spent
together are irreplaceable.
We all worked so hard
and put on that Orchestra together.
This can't be the end...
I won't accept it.
Lavie-san...
Well, I mean!
The five of us are LiGHTs, right?
I don't want to be a trio now!
I mean... I feel the same way.
I want Tia-chan and Rose-chan to be with us, too.
That's all I want right now.
But...
Um...
We all want the five of us
to be together, right?
Tiara-san and Rosetta-san
are headed to Bristol right now.
Then there's just one thing for us to do.
Yeah... Yeah, you're right, Lyn-chan!
Why didn't we think of that sooner?
Right?
Ashley!
Yeah, let's go!
Wait! Are you actually
planning to go to Bristol?
But what are you going to do
once you're there?
We'll figure all that out later!
But...
I think that's fine.
You said so yourself earlier.
That a bond is a treasure.
And treasures are precious.
Not to mention...
I mean, we only got expelled.
I don't think we're going
to be able to stop them.
Let's do what we think is best for us!
Tomorrow's more important
than today anyway.
I'm pretty sure today is important, too...
Make sure you show us
your Orchestra again someday.
Of course!
We promise!
Hey there, miss.
Do you mind being our guide?
What are you all doing here?
We'll go with you!
To go get Tia-chan!
Eh? Get Tia?
Don't even worry about it.
We can't let ourselves be separated!
We'll tell you the details along the way.
Okay! Let's go, sir.
You've got it.
To Bristol!
窓の外は 優しい月明かり そっと
mado no soto wa yasashii tsukiakari sotto
Outside the window, the gentle moonlight is shining softly
灯り消して 夢の橋を渡ろう
akari keshite yume no hashi wo watarou
Put out the lights and cross the bridge of dreams
消えそうで消えないヒカリが今
kie soude kienai hikari ga ima
The weakening yet everlasting light is now
まぶたの向こうの世界に広がった
mabuta no mukou no sekai ni hirogatta
Spreading out into the world behind my eyelids
色んな想いが溢れて
ironna omoi ga afurete
Various feelings are overflowing
キラキラ眩しく輝いてる
kirakira mabushiku kagayaiteru
sparklingly and dazzlingly shining
ずっと
zutto
Forever
It's shining stars
明日はどんな日になるかな
ashita wa donna hi ni naru kana
I wonder what kind of day tomorrow will be
心に映し出す景色は
kokoro ni utsushidasu keshiki wa
The scenery that is reflected in my heart
期待 涙 夢の 全部が重なった
kitai namida yume no zenbu ga kasanatta
Expectations, tears, and dreams, all of it bottled up in my heart
私のプラネタリウム
watashi no planetarium
My planetarium
ほら
hora
Look, in that star that is shining the brightest
一番輝いている あの星に
ichiban kagayaiteiru ano hoshi ni
願いかけて「おやすみ」
negai kakete oyasumi
A wish is enclosed: "Good night"