They're the Magical Monsters
extermination squad.
I see...
Thank you.
You're back.
Onee-chan...
ひたすら描いてた虹の色
I kept drawing rainbow colours over and over
hitasura kaiteta niji no iro
もう七色じゃ足りないから
Seven colours are not enough
mou nanairo ja tarinai kara
毎日はすでにいつもを
Everyday leaps over the "usual" and enters a new chapter
mainichi wa sude ni itsumo wo
飛び越えて新章なのさ
tobikoete shinshou nano sa
物語は遥か彼方へ
The story is going beyond
monogatari wa haruka kanata e
心で鳴り出す鐘の音が
The bell toll in my heart
kokoro de naridasu kane no ne ga
少しずつ大きくなってゆく
is getting louder bit by bit
sukoshi zutsu ookiku natte yuku
その高鳴りを信じて
Believe in the excitement
sono takanari wo shinjite
一歩を踏み出せたなら
And take one step forward
ippo wo fumidaseta nara
想像以上のチカラに変わってるよ
It'll give me more power than I ever imagined
souzou ijouno chikara ni kawatteru yo
絶対なんてない
Can't be for sure
zettai nante nai
なにも
Nothing
nanimo
確信はできない
There's no guarantee
kakushin wa dekinai
だれも
No one
daremo
でもあきらめない
But I won't give up
demo akiramenai
だから
That's why
dakara
進んでくことが
I can still move forward
susundeku koto ga
できるよ
I can still move forward
dekiru yo
ここには魔法があるから
Because there's magic right in here
koko ni wa mahou ga aru kara
だって星より輝きだしたのに
It started to be brighter than the stars
datte hoshi yori kagayaki dashita no ni
立ち止まれるはずもないから
I can't stop now
tachidomareru hazu mo nai kara
時代はついに新しい幕開けを迎えたのさ
It entered into a new era
jidai wa tsui ni atarashii makuake wo mukaeta no sa
溢れた想いを輝石に込めて
Placing this overflowing feelings into this gem
afureta omoi wo kiseki ni komete
未来の方へ
And go beyond the future
saki no hou e
Onee-chan, I...
This is why I told you
that you shouldn't go.
You don't ever have to think
about being a witch.
Ti... a... ra... sa... ma!
Anna.
Welcome home.
Honestly, what were you thinking?!
You went all the way
to Malmcester all alone?
Do you realize who you are?!
And you not contacting us
even once is unheard of!
I'm sorry I left without permission. But—
No ifs, ands, or buts!
Do you realize how worried we all were?!
And that's exactly why Eliza-sama—
What about my sister?
Nothing. I just wish you were
as tame as your sister.
You're turning more and more
into Louise-sama every day.
Where are Mother and the others?
She's currently heading to Dortgart
in order to attend the Witches' Council.
I see. She really does love
going to other countries.
She's not going there to play, you know.
I know, I know.
Um, Onee-chan...
Why can't I become a witch?
That's enough.
I'm finally better, so I want to do what I want.
I want to see just how far I can go!
And yet, you got expelled.
But that's... I just—
You need to be more aware of the fact
that you're the Second Princess of Waleland.
You don't need to worry about
becoming anything more or less.
Then why did you become a witch, Onee-chan?
I am currently fulfilling
my duties as the princess.
I want to be a witch...
I want to be just like you, Onee-chan!
You can't become a witch just from aspirations.
We're done talking about this.
Wow! They all bloomed beautifully.
Tiara, I'll show you something super special.
Wow!
It almost looks like the sky!
They'll go back to normal
after enough time passes.
You're going to become a witch, right, Onee-chan?
Yes. That's my dream.
You're going to be the best witch ev—
Tiara!
Hang in there! Let's get you
back to bed, okay?
Okay...
Are you sure I can have this?
Yes. It's your 13th birthday present.
Thank you...
It looks perfect on you.
Make sure you take good care—
Are you okay?
I just have a little cough, is all.
Now, would you like me to sing for you?
Yeah! I love your songs!
Oh, and you only love my songs?
I love you, too, silly!
Look, Onee-chan!
I'm all better now.
I feel like I can do anything now!
Onee-chan?
Tiara-sama, please don't dwell on this too much.
Would you like some fruit for dessert?
Mm.
Please don't be too angry with Eliza-sama.
We're finally here.
Ow...
I can't believe it took almost three days...
My butt's going to split...
This way, everyone.
How is she okay?
Does she have a butt of steel?
Hold up, Rose-chan!
You may not pass without permission!
I am the daughter of
the master of Alnwick, Rosetta.
I would like to request
an audience with Princess Tiara.
I will go get confirmation,
so I request that you wait until then.
How long will that take?
Well... Probably three days.
Three days?
That's a civil servant for you.
Hey.
All right. We will come back then.
What do we do now?
I mean...
We'll just have to wait.
Aw, and I thought we'd be having
a feast tonight at the palace.
That's what you were thinking about?
Sorry, I was, too.
Well, why wouldn't we?
Hot!
—Hot, hot, hot, hot!
—What are you doing, you Silly Rabbit?
For now, we can just stay at my place.
Is it nearby?
It's about half a day by carriage.
Carriages again?
Why don't we stay at an inn tonight?
So hey, can't we just sneak in to see her?
You know. Using those things.
Nettie, you've gotten really good.
I can't just always keep relying on all of you.
Stop.
It's a dead end...
It's quite sturdy.
Should we use magic?
Reinforcement magic?
That'll take too much out of you.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Take that!
Wow, you did both at once.
I see. You used thermal expansion.
Huh? Thermal wha...?
You mean you didn't know this would happen?
Nah, I was just fooling around,
mixing stuff together,
and it was a lot of fun breaking stuff!
Really?
Let's get going.
We somehow made it in safely.
Let's proceed by hiding
behind things here on out.
Hurry, please...
Rose-chan, you're heavy...
Security sure is heavy...
Which way should we go?
There's a shortcut over there
if we can just get over there.
This calls for a decoy...
And by that, I mean Lavie.
Mfhy mfe?!
No, leave this to me.
Who's there?!
What's wrong?
I thought I heard a noise...
I'm sure it was just a frog or some bugs.
You think so?
I thought I felt a suspicious presence...
I can't believe you can use
such advanced magic.
It's far from perfect yet, but...
Um...
I'm stuck.
Ready, and...
Ow, ow, ow!
It's dark. It's cramped. It's scary.
Hang on a sec.
And now...
We go this way.
I'm surprised you remember.
Tia and I found this route
when we were little and exploring.
I guess you two were pretty rambunctious.
Lynette?!
'Sup?
I just... felt something on my foot.
It's just a mouse.
That startled me.
Looks like we're clear.
Where are we?
The shrine.
It's Flora-sama.
From here on out,
we'll have to move through the palace.
We'll probably be hard to spot if we use
that Transparency Magic again.
I don't have enough strength to use it again.
Guess we'll just have to sneak about then.
They spotted us!
Hey! Halt!
Ashley, you dummy!
After them!
This way!
Who goes there?!
What's going on?
It appears that there are
intruders in the palace.
Deal with them immediately.
Yes, ma'am!
Crap!
Ashley-san?!
Honour the name of the witch of
this ritual and dance, servant!
Wait, you're—
That's enough!
You can't run forever!
Ugh, they just won't give up.
Lavie!
Anna?
Yes? My stars! If it isn't Lady Rose!
It's been so long.
Honestly. If you're going to play
hide and seek, find somewhere else.
I'm sorry this is sudden, but please, help us.
I beg your pardon?
Eliza-sama! You're Eliza-sama, aren't you?!
I absolutely love Ray, and—
What are you doing here?
Did you actually come all this way to see Tiara?
How do you know about us...
You can cancel the alert.
Are you certain?
Yes.
Tiara-sama, I'm coming in.
—Tia-san!
—Tiara!
Wait, what are you doing here?!
We were all worried about you.
We couldn't just end things
like that, could we?
There's still so much we want to do together!
And you still haven't
bought me my Hamburg steak.
Everyone... But we were expelled...
So what?
Huh?!
Tia, what do you want to do?
I... I still want to be a witch,
just like my sister.
In that case—
But my sister told me...
...that I can't become a witch
just by aspirations.
I mean, she's sorta right.
Well, you're just you.
Yeah. Lavie's right.
No matter how hard you try,
you won't be able to become Eliza-sama.
They're right. You're you, Tiara.
I'm... me?
Everyone has their own way to their dreams.
That's fine if it's just an aspiration.
But if you keep chasing someone forever,
won't you lose your own way?
My own way?
I...
I want to be a witch that can cheer people up
just like my sister did for me.
That feeling hasn't gone away.
But after we did that Orchestra, I thought...
At that moment, my heart
was dancing with happiness
and I let my emotions get the better of me.
I was concentrating more on myself
than the people watching us.
And yet, I have the nerve to say that
I want to become a witch to help others...
I think that's fine, though.
Don't you think if you're
having fun and spreading cheer,
it'll also make others happy?
Yeah! You need to think about yourself first!
You should actually think
about those around you more.
You were absolutely dazzling
that night, Tiara-san.
That's why I know you'll be able
to become someone's light!
That's just how you do it, Tia-chan!
How I do it...
You just need to strive
to be who you want to be.
That goes for you and the rest of us.
Tia.
Yeah.
Thank you, everyone.
I'm going to keep doing my best.
I'm going to be a witch
that only I can ever be!
Heck yeah!
That's our Tiara.
Believe in yourself!
No...
I'm going to believe in us...
I'm going to believe in LiGHTs!
Now that that's settled,
we need to figure out the next step.
Anna! Get us some tea, please!
Of course.
Melissa and the others said that?
Yes. They made us
realize something important.
Being with you is way more important
than us being expelled!
You're making me blush...
Aw, no need to be shy!
This is... amazing!
It's pudding.
It's so sweet and melts in your mouth!
It makes you feel so happy.
It's very different from the pudding I know...
So about what we're going to do now...
I don't think getting back into
the academy will be that simple.
Y-Yeah, I figured...
But with the five of us together,
we'll be able to figure it out!
We are LiGHTs, after all!
Wait, did I say something weird?
No, that's not it.
You've changed, Lyn-chan.
So...
At this rate,
maybe we don't need to concentrate
on Flora Girl's Academy so much.
There are other witches'
academies in other countries.
Really?
Let's try to become witches that way.
But... I want to do Orchestras, too.
I do, too.
We all feel the same.
Let's improve our singing and dancing.
Then we'll go back to Malmcester
and show them our stuff!
We'll make the academy
regret expelling us. Right?
Yeah...
Maybe we can just go to
all the neighboring countries.
We're going seaside!
You mean we're going worldwide.
How's that any different?
It just is, okay?
What's that supposed to mean?
It just is.
There's no need to rush.
I don't get it.
Yes.
Let's take our time to think about it.
I want to check out the library.
I'll have to make us more outfits.
I wanna eat more of
that yummy stuff we just had.
You already finished yours?
Have as much as you'd like.
Sweet!
Maybe I'll have another, too...
You're so greedy, Ashley.
Look who's talking.
誰でも胸の中には
dare demo mune no naka ni wa
Inside of everybody's hearts
弱さを抱えてるから
yowa sa wo kakaeterukara
holds some weakness
たとえ 空が重い雲に覆われても
tatoe sora ga omoi kumo ni ouwaretemo
Even if the sky is overcast with heavy clouds
思い出してわたしのこと
omoi dashite watashi no koto
Just remember things about me
ほら
hora
Come on
その瞳に その心に
sono hitomi ni sono kokoro ni
In those eyes, in that heart
輝きが灯るように
kagayaki ga tomoru you ni
A radiance is being lit
その瞳に その心に
sono hitomi ni sono kokoro ni
In those eyes, in that heart
宿す 希望
yadosu kibou
A hope is being held
その涙も その痛みも
sono namida mo sono itami mo
Take those tears, take that pain
今日で終わりますように
kyou de owarimasu you ni
Let’s end it today
ちっぽけでも キミを照らす光
chippoke demo kimi wo terasu hikari
Shining on you, a tiny little light
わたしの名は、光
watashi no na wa, hikari
My name is, Light
We are LiGHTs. You're my Shine.
We are LIGHTs. You’re my shine
Sing along!
We are LiGHTs. You're my Shine.
We are LIGHTs. You’re my shine
その涙も その痛みも
sono namida mo sono itami mo
Take those tears, take that pain
今日で終わりますように
kyou de owarimasu you ni
let’s end it today
ちっぽけでも キミを照らす光
chippoke demo kimi wo terasu hikari
Shining on you, a tiny little light
わたしの名は、光
watashi no na wa, hikari
My name is, Light
Yes!
Angelica.
I'm busy right now, so bug me later.
I'm going to let you know first.
Chloe?
Are you serious?
Very.